<localization>
    <set id="steam-shortdescription">
        <string lang="de">Das Automatisierungs-Roguelike. Bau deine eigenen Skills, indem du Module miteinander verkabelst. Konstruiere irre Maschinen, zappe die Monster und löse wilde Kettenreaktionen aus.</string>
        <string lang="en">The engineering roguelike. Construct your own skills by wiring up modules. Build crazy machines to zap the monsters and trigger satisfying chain reactions.</string>
        <string lang="fr">Roguelike Deckbuilder rencontre jeu d'automatisation. Construisez vos actions en connectant des modules. Composez des machines complexes, déclenchez des réactions en chaîne sauvages, manipulez la chronologie et remettez le courant dans un monde où le temps est détraqué.</string>
        <string lang="zh">Roguelike Deckbuilder 是一款自动化编程游戏，你需要连接各种模块化装备与敌人战斗。生产、管理能量，掌控时间线，战胜随机生成的敌人，在时空错乱的世界中恢复人类的能源供应。</string>
        <string lang="jp">ローグライクなデッキ ビルダーがモジュラー シンセサイザーと出会う。モジュールを接続して戦闘アクションを構築します。エネルギーを生成して管理し、タイムラインを操作し、手続き上の脅威を打ち負かし、タイムシフトされた世界で電気の回復を試みます。</string>
        <string lang="ru">Колодостроительный рогалик встретил игру про автоматизацию. Создай свои собственные умения соединяя модули. Постройте свою комплексную машину, активирующую буйную цепочку реакций. Управляйте временной линией и запитайте снова мир, в которой время вышло из строя.</string>
        <string lang="es">Roguelike Deckbuilder se encuentra con un juego de automatizaciòn. Construye tus propias acciones conectando módulos. Crea complejas máquinas y provoca salvajes efectos en cadena, manipula la línea temporal e intenta recuperar el poder en un mundo donde el tiempo es inestable.</string>
        <string lang="kr">Roguelike Deckbuilder는 자동화 게임을 만납니다. 모듈을 연결하여 전투 행동을 구성하십시오. 에너지를 생성하고 관리하고 타임 라인을 조작하고 절차적 위협을 물리치고 시간이 불안정한 세계에서 전력을 되찾으십시오.</string>
        <string lang="pt-br">Roguelike Deckbuilder encontra jogo de automação. Construa suas ações de combate conectando módulos. Gere e gerencie energia, manipule a linha do tempo, supere ameaças de procedimento e tente recuperar a energia em um mundo onde o tempo está instável.</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Інженерний рогалік. Розвивайте власні навички, підключаючи модулі. Створюйте божевільні машини, щоб знищувати монстрів і запускати чудові ланцюгові реакції.</string>
</set>
    <set id="steam-description">
        <string lang="de">[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerwireup.png[/img]
Bau deine Aktionen, indem du Module miteinander verkabelst. Konstruiere irre Maschinen, erstelle starke Builds und zappe die Monster mit wilden Kettenreaktionen!

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/rack.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerzap.png[/img]
Jede Runde musst du dich entscheiden, wohin du deine Energie leitest: In dein Blaster-Modul? Solltest du einen Heiltrank anbrechen? Oder speicherst du deine Energie in einer Batterie, um einen noch größeren Zug vorzubereiten?

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/battle.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerturnbased.png[/img]
Züge können in der Zeit taktisch vor- und zurückgeschoben werden: Weiche Vulkanausbrüchen oder Blitschlägen aus, schlüpfe vor deine Gegner auf der Zeitleiste oder stoße sie in eine verheerende Grav.-Spitze.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/timeline3.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerroguelike.png[/img]
Dein Abenteuer führt dich durch fremdartige Biome, in denen knifflige Gegnern nur darauf warten, dir den Tag zu vermiesen. Verkabel deine Racks smart, um mit den zunehmend gefährlichen Bedrohungen fertig zu werden.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/levels.gif[/img]
[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/landscape2.png[/img]</string>
        <string lang="en">[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerwireup.png[/img]
Build your own abilities by wiring together modules. Construct crazy machines, create powerful builds and zap the monsters with insane chain reactions!

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/rack.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerzap.png[/img]
Every turn you have to decide where you want to put your energy: Into your blaster module? Do you have to crack a healing potion? Or do you store energy in a battery to prepare an even bigger move next turn?


[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/battle.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerturnbased.png[/img]
Turns can be tactically pushed and pulled forward or backward in time: Dodge volcano eruptions and lightning strikes, slip before your enemies on the timeline or throw them into a devastating Grav-Spike.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/timeline3.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerroguelike.png[/img]
Your adventure leads you through strange biomes where tricky enemies try to ruin your day. Compose your racks wisely to deal with the procedurally generated and progressively dangerous threats.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/levels.gif[/img]
[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/landscape2.png[/img]</string>
        <string lang="fr">[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerwireup.png[/img]
Construisez vos capacités à partir de [b]modules[/b] spécialisés. Certains génèrent de l'énergie, certains la modifient ou la stockent et d'autres la transforment en effets. [b]Construisez des structures puissantes[/b] pour zapper vos ennemis ou conserver charge pour moments de besoin.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/rack.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerzap.png[/img]
Chaque tour de combat pose des [b]défis tactiques[/b] où diriger votre énergie : vers votre module blaster pour blesser les monstres ? Dans un décélérateur pour contrôler la chronologie ? Faut-il casser une potion de soin ? Ou le stockez-vous dans une batterie et préparez-vous un mouvement encore plus ambitieux au prochain tour ?


[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/battle.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerturnbased.png[/img]
Dans ce monde brisé, [b]la cause et l'effet[/b] sont déséquilibrés. Maîtrisez l'art de Gravitonics pour avancer [b]en avant ou en arrière dans le temps[/b] : évitez les éruptions volcaniques et les éclairs, glissez-vous devant vos ennemis ou lancez-les dans un Grav Spike dévastateur.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/timeline3.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerroguelike.png[/img]
Votre aventure vous mène à travers une variété de biomes où des groupes d'ennemis rusés tentent de gâcher votre journée. Composez et corrigez judicieusement vos racks pour faire face aux menaces [b]générées de manière procédurale[/b] et progressivement dangereuses.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/levels.gif[/img]
[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/landscape2.png[/img]</string>
        <string lang="zh">[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerwireup.png[/img]
通过连接各种[b]模块[/b]来创造角色的不同能力。一些模块生产能量、一些能存储或修改能量类型、剩下的则将能量转化为效果。[b]搭建强大的结构[/b]来消灭敌人或在把能量存入电池以备不时之需。

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/rack.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerzap.png[/img]
每个回合将能量引导到哪都是一个[b]战术问题[/b]：是导入爆能枪模块直接攻击敌人，还是导入减速枪来控制战场上的时间线？是使用治疗药水恢复生命，还是将能量存入电池准备下个回合打一发大的？

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/battle.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerturnbased.png[/img]

在这个破碎的世界中，[b]因果律[/b]都被破坏了。通过灵活操控引力荷[b]在时间线上前后移动[/b]来：躲避火山喷发和雷击，从敌人面前溜过，甚至将敌人送入强力的的引力尖峰。

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/timeline3.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerroguelike.png[/img]
你的冒险将穿越各种生物群落，各种难缠的敌群都有可能毁掉你。巧妙地连接机架上的各种模块，来应对[b]随机生成的[/b]不断增加的威胁。

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/levels.gif[/img]
[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/landscape2.png[/img]</string>
        <string lang="jp">[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerwireup.png[/img]
特殊な[b]モジュール[/b]を接続して、キャラクターのスキルを構築します。エネルギーを生成するものもあれば、エネルギーを変換または保存するものもあれば、エネルギーを効果に変えるものもあります。[b]強力な構造物を構築[/b]して敵に衝撃を与えたり、必要なときに備えてエネルギーをバッテリーに蓄えたりします。

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/rack.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerzap.png[/img]
各戦闘ターンは[b]戦術的な課題[/b]を提示します。どこにエネルギーを向けるべきですか? モンスターを傷つけるためのブラスター モジュールに? タイムラインを制御するレデューサーに? 治癒ポーションを使うべきですか？それとも、バッテリーを充電して、次のターンにさらに野心的な動きを準備しますか?


[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/battle.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerturnbased.png[/img]
この粉々になった世界では、[b]原因と結果[/b]は一致していません。グラビトニクスの技術をマスターして、[b]タイムライン上で戦闘ターンを前後に動かします[/b]: 火山の噴火や落雷をかわし、敵の前にジャンプし、壊滅的な重力スパイクを敵に放ちます。

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/timeline3.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerroguelike.png[/img]
あなたの冒険は、トリッキーな敵のグループがあなたの一日を台無しにしようとするさまざまなバイオームを通り抜けます。[b]システムをインテリジェントに構成し[/b]、手続き的に生成され、ますます危険性を増す脅威に対処します。

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/levels.gif[/img]
[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/landscape2.png[/img]</string>
        <string lang="ru">[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerwireup.png[/img]
Собирайте свои навыки из [b]специализированных модулей[/b]. Некоторые генерируют энергию, другие изменяют или сохраняют ее, а другие превращают ее в эффекты. [b]Стройте мощные структуры[/b], чтобы уничтожить врагов или сохранить заряд батареи в момент нужды.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/rack.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerzap.png[/img]
Каждый ход боя представляет собой [b]тактические вызовы[/b]: куда направить свою энергию? На модуль бластера, чтобы нанести урон монстрам? На замедлитель, чтобы контролировать таймлайн? Вы должны использовать лечебное зелье? Или вы сохраните её в батарее и подготовите грандиозный план для следующего хода?


[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/battle.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerturnbased.png[/img]
В этом разрушенном мире [b]причина и следствие[/b] не совпадают. Овладейте мастерством гравитоника и [b]перемещайте ходы боя вперед и назад по таймлайну[/b]: уклоняйтесь от извержений вулканов и молний, прыгайте перед врагами и выпускайте разрушительные гравитационные шипы на врагов.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/timeline3.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerroguelike.png[/img]
Ваше приключение пройдет через различные биомы, в которых коварные группы врагов попытаются испортить ваш день. [b]Интеллектуально настройте систему[/b] и справляйтесь с угрозами, которые генерируются процедурно и становятся все более опасными.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/levels.gif[/img]
[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/landscape2.png[/img]
    </string>
        <string lang="es">[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerwireup.png[/img]
Construye tus habilidades a partir de [b]módulos[/b] especializados. Unos generan energía, otros la modifican o almacenan y otros la convierten en efectos. [b]Construye poderosas estructuras[/b] para eliminar a tus enemigos o conservar la carga de las baterías para los momentos de necesidad.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/rack.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerzap.png[/img]
Cada turno de combate plantea [b]desafíos tácticos[/b] en cuanto a dónde dirigir tu energía: ¿Hacia tu módulo blaster para dañar a los monstruos? ¿A un desacelerador para controlar la línea temporal? ¿Deberías tomar una poción curativa? ¿O la guardas en una batería y preparas un movimiento aún más ambicioso en el siguiente turno?


[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/battle.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerturnbased.png[/img]
En este mundo destrozado [b]causa y efecto[/b] están fuera de lugar. Domina el arte de la gravitónica para mover turnos [b]hacia adelante o hacia atrás en el tiempo[/b]: esquiva erupciones volcánicas y rayos, deslízate ante tus enemigos o lánzalos a un Pico Gravitatorio devastador.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/timeline3.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerroguelike.png[/img]
Tu aventura te lleva a través de una variedad de biomas donde grupos de enemigos astutos intentan arruinarte el día. Arma y repara tus bastidores de manera inteligente para hacer frente a amenazas [b]proceduralmente generadas[/b] y progresivamente más peligrosas.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/levels.gif[/img]
[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/landscape2.png[/img]</string>
    <string lang="kr">[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerwireup.png[/img]
[b]전문 모듈[/b]에서 기술을 구축하십시오. 일부는 에너지를 생성하고 다른 일부는 에너지를 변형하거나 저장하고 다른 일부는 효과로 변환합니다. [b]강력한 구조물을 건설[/b]하여 적을 제거하거나 다음 턴에 필요한 배터리 충전을 유지하십시오.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/rack.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerzap.png[/img]
각 전투 턴은 [b]전술적 도전[/b]을 제기합니다. 몬스터를 공격하기 위해 블래스터 모듈로 에너지를 어디에 사용해야합니까? 타임 라인을 제어하기 위해 감속기에? 치유 물약을 부수는 것이 좋습니까? 아니면 배터리에 넣어 다음 턴에 더욱 야심찬 움직임을 준비합니까?


[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/battle.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerturnbased.png[/img]
이 파괴 된 세계에서 [b]원인과 결과[/b]는 일치하지 않습니다. 시간을 [b]앞뒤로 이동[/b]하는 중력학의 기술을 마스터하십시오. 화산 분화 및 번개를 피하거나 적에게 미친 중력 스파이크를 발사하십시오.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/timeline3.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerroguelike.png[/img]
모험은 다양한 생물 군계가 당신의 날을 망치려고하는 다양한 생물 군계를 통해 진행됩니다. [b]절차적으로 생성 된[/b] 위협과 점차적으로 위험해지는 위협에 대처하기 위해 똑똑하게 랙을 구성하고 수리하십시오.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/levels.gif[/img]
[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/landscape2.png[/img]</string>
    <string lang="pt-br">[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerwireup.png[/img]
Construa suas habilidades a partir de [b]módulos[/b] especializados. Alguns geram energia, outros a modificam ou armazenam e outros a transformam em efeitos. [b]Construa estruturas poderosas[/b] para eliminar seus inimigos ou conservar a carga das baterias para momentos de necessidade.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/rack.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerzap.png[/img]
Cada turno de combate apresenta [b]desafios táticos[/b] para onde direcionar sua energia: para o seu módulo blaster para ferir os monstros? Em um desacelerador para controlar a linha do tempo? Você deve quebrar uma poção de cura? Ou você o armazena em uma bateria e prepara um movimento ainda mais ambicioso no próximo turno?


[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/battle.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerturnbased.png[/img]
Neste mundo destruído, [b]causa e efeito[/b] estão desarticulados. Domine a arte da gravitonica para mover turnos [b]para frente ou para trás no tempo[/b]: esquive-se de erupções vulcânicas e raios, deslize-se antes de seus inimigos ou jogue-os em um pico Grav. devastador.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/timeline3.gif[/img]

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerroguelike.png[/img]
Sua aventura o leva por uma variedade de biomas onde grupos de inimigos astutos tentam arruinar seu dia. Componha e conserte seus racks com sabedoria para lidar com ameaças [b]geradas processualmente[/b] e progressivamente perigosas.

[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/levels.gif[/img]
[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/landscape2.png[/img]</string>
    		<string lang="uk">[img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerwireup.png[/img] Розвивайте власні здібності, об’єднуючи модулі. Конструюйте божевільні машини, створюйте потужні збірки та знищуйте монстрів за допомогою божевільної ланцюгової реакції! [img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/rack.gif[/img] [img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerzap.png[/img] Кожного ходу ви повинні вирішувати, куди ви хочете вкладати свою енергію: у свій бластерний модуль? Чи потрібно випити цілюще зілля? Або направити енергію в акумулятор, щоб підготувати ще більшу ланцюгову реакцію у наступному кроці? [img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/battle.gif[/img] [img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerturnbased.png[/img] Опануйте граві-майстерність і переміщуйте ходи бою вперед і назад: уникайте вивержень вулканів і блискавок, прослизніть через ворогів на часовій шкалі або киньте їх у нищівну гравітаційну бурю. [img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/timeline3.gif[/img] [img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/headerroguelike.png[/img] Ваша пригода веде вас через дивні біоми, де підступні вороги намагаються зіпсувати вам день. Компонуйте свої стелажі з розумом, щоб мати справу з процедурно генерованими та прогресивно небезпечними загрозами. [img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/levels.gif[/img] [img]{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/landscape2.png[/img]</string>
</set>
    <set id="steam-credentials1">
        <string lang="de">This roguelike deckbuilder has a great twist</string>
        <string lang="en">This roguelike deckbuilder has a great twist</string>
        <string lang="fr">Ce deckbuilder roguelike a un super twist</string>
        <string lang="zh">这个卡牌Rogue的创意太让我惊喜了</string>
        <string lang="jp">このローグライク デッキ ビルダーには驚くべきひねりがあります</string>
        <string lang="ru">Этот колодостроительный рогалик имеет отличный твист</string>
        <string lang="es">Este roguelike deckbuilder tiene un gran giro</string>
        <string lang="kr">이 로그라이크 덱 빌더는 훌륭한 트위스트가 있습니다</string>
        <string lang="pt-br">Este roguelike deckbuilder tem um ótimo twist</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Цей колодабудівний рогалик має відмінний твіст</string>
</set>
    <set id="steam-credentials2">
        <string lang="de">An extremely unusual take on the genre</string>
        <string lang="en">An extremely unusual take on the genre</string>
        <string lang="fr">Une approche extrêmement inhabituelle du genre</string>
        <string lang="zh">在同品类游戏里极其罕见的设计</string>
        <string lang="jp">ジャンルに対する非常に珍しい見方</string>
        <string lang="ru">Чрезвычайно необычный подход к жанру</string>
        <string lang="es">Una versión extremadamente inusual del género</string>
        <string lang="kr">장르에 대한 매우 특이한 접근</string>
        <string lang="pt-br">Uma abordagem extremamente incomum do gênero</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Надзвичайно незвичайний погляд на жанр</string>
</set>
        <set id="steam-credentials3">
        <string lang="de">HOLY SH** YES</string>
        <string lang="en">HOLY SH** YES</string>
        <string lang="fr">HOLY SH** YES</string>
        <string lang="zh">我*，太帅了</string>
        <string lang="jp">なんてこった！！</string>
        <string lang="ru">БЛ*ТЬ ДА</string>
        <string lang="es">¡HOSTIA P**A SÍ!</string>
        <string lang="kr">HOLY SH** YES</string>
        <string lang="pt-br">HOLY SH** YES</string>
    		<string lang="uk">ДІДЬКО ТАК</string>
</set>
</localization>