<localization>
<set id="advice-camp">
		<string lang="de">Kaufe $campresource$ während jedes Camp-Besuchs, um nach und nach die Gebäude auszubauen.</string>
		<string lang="en">Buy $campresource$ during each camp visit to gradually upgrade camp buildings</string>
        <string lang="fr">Achetez des $campresource$ à chaque visite au camp pour améliorer progressivement les bâtiments du camp.</string>
        <string lang="zh">在每次营地访问期间购买$campresource$，以逐步升级营地建筑。</string>
        <string lang="ja">各キャンプ訪問時に$campresource$を購入して、キャンプの建物を徐々にアップグレードしましょう。</string>
        <string lang="ru">Покупайте $campresource$ во время каждого визита в лагерь, чтобы постепенно улучшать здания лагеря.</string>
        <string lang="es">Compra $campresource$ durante cada visita al campamento para mejorar gradualmente los edificios del campamento.</string>
        <string lang="kr">각 캠프 방문 시 $campresource$를 구매하여 캠프 건물을 점진적으로 업그레이드하세요.</string>
        <string lang="pt-br">Compre $campresource$ durante cada visita ao acampamento para melhorar gradualmente os edifícios do acampamento.</string>
        <string lang="zh-tw">在每次營地訪問期間購買$campresource$，以逐步升級營地建築。</string>
        <string lang="uk">Купуйте $campresource$ під час кожного візиту до табору, щоб поступово покращувати будівлі табору.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-cracked">
		<string lang="de">Horte Module mit $cracked$ nicht, sondern nutze ihren starken einmaligen Effekt, um eine gute Wertung zu erhalten oder einen Kampf zügig zu beenden.</string>
		<string lang="en">Don't hoard $cracked$ modules, but use their strong one-time effect to secure a good rating or end a combat that is getting out of hand.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Ne stockez pas les modules à usage unique ($cracked$), mais utilisez leurs puissant effet unique pour obtenir une note $special$ ou gagner un combat qui vous échappe.</string>
		<string lang="zh">与其囤积$cracked$模块，不如利用它们强大的一次性效果来取得高评分或结束难缠的敌人。</string>
		<string lang="jp">$cracked$モジュールを出し惜しみせず、$br$一回限りの強力な効果を用いて高評価を確保したり、$br$手に負えない戦闘を終えたりしよう。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Не запасайтесь одноразовымы ($cracked$) модулями, а используйте их сильные одноразовые эффекты, чтобы получить оценку $special$ или выиграть бой, который выходит из-под контроля.</string>
		<string lang="es">No acumules módulos ($cracked$) de un solo uso, aprovecha su fuerte efecto individual para asegurar una calificación $special$ o ganar un combate que se está saliendo de control.</string>
		<string lang="kr">$cracked$ 상태의 모듈은 너무 쌓아두지 마시고, 강력한 일회용 효과로 높은 등급을 확보하거나, 감당할 수 없을 것 같은 전투를 마무리 지으세요.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Não acumule módulos de uso único ($cracked$), mas use seu forte efeito único para garantir uma classificação $special$ ou terminar um combate que está saindo do controle.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">與其囤積$cracked$模組，不如利用它們強大的一次性效果來取得高評分或結束難纏的敵人。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Не накопичуй крихкі $cracked$ модулі, використовуй їхній потужний ефект, щоб отримати гарний рейтинг або завершити бій, що виходить з-під контролю.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-deceleration">
		<string lang="de">Unterschätze nicht die Wirksamkeit,$br$einen Gegner einfach zu verlangsamen.</string>
		<string lang="en">Dont underestimate the effectiveness of simply$br$slowing down an enemy.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Ne sous-estimez pas l'efficacité de simplement ralentir un ennemi.</string>
		<string lang="zh">不要小看单纯减速敌人的作用。</string>
		<string lang="jp">敵の行動を遅らせる効果を侮らないように。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Не недооценивайте эффективность простого замедления врага.</string>
		<string lang="es">No subestimes la efectividad de, simplemente, ralentizar a un enemigo.</string>
		<string lang="kr">적을 느려지게 만드는 것의 유용성을 과소평가하지 마세요.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Não subestime a eficácia de simplesmente desacelerar um inimigo.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">不要小看單純減速敵人的作用。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Не варто недооцінювати ефективності уповільнення ворога.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-draft">
		<string lang="de">Wenn du Loot-Module auswählst, achte auf eine gute Balance zwischen Energiequellen, Durchsatzmodulen und Effektoren.</string>
		<string lang="en">Key to a good build is a nice balance between energy sources, passthrough modules and effectors.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Lorsque vous choisissez des modules comme butin, trouvez un bon équilibre entre les sources d'énergie, les modules de relais et les effecteurs.</string>
		<string lang="zh">优秀模组的构建，在于能量型、中继型、效果型三种模块之间的良好平衡。</string>
		<string lang="jp">優れたビルドの鍵は、エネルギー源、中継モジュール、$br$エフェクターのバランスにある。</string>
		<string lang="ru">При выборе модулей как добычи, найдите хороший баланс между источниками энергии, пропускными модулями и эффекторами.</string>
		<string lang="es">Al elegir módulos como botín, encuentra un buen equilibrio entre las fuentes de energía, los módulos de traspaso y los módulos con efecto.</string>
		<string lang="kr">좋은 빌드의 핵심은 에너지원과 통과 모듈, 효과 모듈의 균형을 유지하는 것입니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Ao escolher módulos como saque, encontre um bom equilíbrio entre fontes de energia, módulos de transferência e effectors.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">優秀模組的構建，在於能量型、中繼型、效果型三種模組之間的良好平衡。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Ключ до якісної збірки – баланс між джерелами енергії, пропускними модулями та модулями впливу.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-enemies-1">
		<string lang="de">Klicke auf Gegner, um ihre Fähigkeiten zu sehen.$br$Gegner werden immer versuchen, deine Pläne zu durchkreuzen und ihre Verbündeten zu unterstützen.</string>
		<string lang="en">Click on enemies to see their abilities.$br$Enemies will always try to disrupt your plans and support their allies.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Cliquez sur les ennemis pour voir leurs capacités. Les ennemis essaieront toujours de perturber vos plans et de soutenir leurs alliés.</string>
		<string lang="zh">点击敌人来查看他们的技能。他们总是致力于破坏你的计划，并帮助自己的盟友。</string>
		<string lang="jp">敵をクリックで能力を確認できる。$br$敵は常にこちらの計画を妨害し、$br$仲間をサポートしようとする。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Нажмите на врагов, чтобы увидеть их способности. Враги всегда будут пытаться разрушить ваши планы и поддержать своих союзников.</string>
		<string lang="es">Haz clic en los enemigos para ver sus habilidades. Los enemigos siempre intentarán interrumpir tus planes y apoyar a sus aliados.</string>
		<string lang="kr">적들을 클릭해 적의 능력을 확인해보세요. 적은 항상 여러분의 계획을 방해하며 자신의 아군을 지원하려 할 것입니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Clique nos inimigos para ver suas habilidades. Os inimigos sempre tentarão interromper seus planos e apoiar seus aliados.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">點擊敵人來查看他們的技能。他們總是致力於破壞你的計畫，並幫助自己的盟友。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Натискай на ворогів, щоб побачити їхні здібності.$br$Вороги завжди будуть намагатися зірвати твої плани і підтримати своїх союзників.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-enemies-2">
		<string lang="de">Überprüfe die Fähigkeiten der Gegner auf Störquellen$br$wie $grav$ oder $crust$.</string>
		<string lang="en">Check enemy movesets for sources of disruption,$br$such as $grav$ or $crust$.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Vérifiez les mouvements des ennemis pour savoir s'ils peuvent vous perturber, comme $grav$ ou $crust$.</string>
		<string lang="zh">查看敌人是否有干扰技能，如$grav$或$crust$。</string>
		<string lang="jp">妨害のきっかけ、たとえば$grav$や$crust$などの$br$敵の動きを確認しよう。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Проверьте способности врагов на наличие источников помех, таких как $grav$ или $crust$.</string>
		<string lang="es">Revisa los movimientos de los enemigos en busca de fuentes de interrupción, como $grav$ o $crust$.</string>
		<string lang="kr">적이 $grav$나 $crust$ 같은 방해 행동을 취하려 하는지 확인하세요.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Verifique os movimentos do inimigo em busca de fontes de interrupção, como $grav$ ou $crust$.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">查看敵人是否有干擾技能，如$grav$或$crust$。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Зважай на перешкоди серед вмінь ворогів,$br$як от $grav$ або $crust$.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-energy">
		<string lang="de">Jeder Punkt $energy$, den du erzeugen kannst, zählt.</string>
		<string lang="en">Every point of $energy$ you can generate is meaningful.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chaque point d'$energy$ que vous pouvez générer est important.</string>
		<string lang="zh">产出的每一点$energy$都会派上用场。</string>
		<string lang="jp">生み出す$energy$全てを意味あるものにしよう。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Каждый пункт $energy$, который вы можете сгенерировать, важен.</string>
		<string lang="es">Cada punto de $energy$ que puedas generar es importante.</string>
		<string lang="kr">$energy$는 일단 생성하면 유의미하게 사용할 수 있습니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Cada ponto de $energy$ que você pode gerar é significativo.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">產出的每一點$energy$都會派上用場。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Кожна одиниця згенерованої тобою $energy$ має значення.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-energy-2">
		<string lang="de">Versuche, $energy$ auf $sensor$-Modulen$br$nicht verpuffen zu lassen.</string>
		<string lang="en">Try to not let $energy$ on $sensor$ modules dissipate.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Essayez de ne pas laisser l'$energy$ sur les modules $sensor$ se dissiper.</string>
		<string lang="zh">尽量不要浪费传感型模块产出的$energy$。</string>
		<string lang="jp">$sensor$モジュールの$energy$を散逸させないように。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Постарайтесь не допустить рассеивание $energy$ на сенсорных модулях.</string>
		<string lang="es">Intenta no dejar que la $energy$ en los módulos sensores se disipe.</string>
		<string lang="kr">감지기 모듈의 $energy$가 소멸되지 않게 하세요.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Tente não deixar a $energy$ nos módulos de sensores se dissipar.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">儘量不要浪費傳感型模組產出的$energy$。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Намагайся не давати розсіюватися $energyicon$$b$Енергії$/b$ на $sensor$ модулях.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-exhaustion">
		<string lang="de">Wenn du einen $generator$ aktivierst, wird dein nächster Zug um dessen Erschöpfungswert zurückgesetzt.</string>
		<string lang="en">Activating a $generator$ sets your next turn back by its Exhaustion value.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Activer un $generator$ fait reculer votre prochain tour de sa valeur d'épuisement.</string>
		<string lang="zh">激活$generator$会使你的轮次延后等同疲劳值的步长。</string>
		<string lang="jp">$generator$を起動すると、$br$次のターンが消耗の分だけ遅くなる。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Активация $generator$ сбрасывает ваш следующий ход на значение его истощения. </string>
		<string lang="es">Activar un $generator$ retrasa tu siguiente turno por su valor de agotamiento. </string>
		<string lang="kr">$generator$를 활성화할 시 고갈 수치에 따라 다음 턴이 늦춰집니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Ativar um $generator$ define seu próximo turno de volta pelo valor de Exaustão.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">啟動$generator$會使你的輪次延後等同疲勞值的步長。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">При активація $generator$ відтерміновує твій наступний хід на значення виснаження.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-exhaustion-2">
		<string lang="de">Wenn du versuchst, Züge auszurichten, ist es manchmal am klügsten, einen Generator überhaupt nicht zu aktivieren.</string>
		<string lang="en">If you are trying to align turns, sometimes the smartest move is to not activate a generator at all.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Si vous essayez d'aligner les tours, parfois le meilleur mouvement est de ne pas activer du tout un générateur.</string>
		<string lang="zh">如果想对齐轮次，有时最明智的做法是干脆不去激活发生器。</string>
		<string lang="jp">ターンを揃えたいなら、時として発電機を$br$一切起動しないことが最適解になる。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Если вы пытаетесь выровнять ходы, иногда самый умный ход - не активировать генератор вовсе.</string>
		<string lang="es">Si estás tratando de alinear los turnos, a veces el movimiento más inteligente es no activar un generador en absoluto.</string>
		<string lang="kr">턴을 조정하고 싶으시다면, 발전기를 작동시키지 않는 게 가장 좋은 방법일 수도 있습니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Se você está tentando alinhar os turnos, às vezes o movimento mais inteligente é não ativar um gerador de forma alguma.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">如果想對齊輪次，有時最明智的做法是乾脆不去啟動發生器。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Для того щоб вирівняти ходи, іноді краще взагалі не активувати генератор.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-fire">
		<string lang="de">$fire$ kann gelöscht werden, indem das Modul mit $cooldown$ oder $outoforder$ versehen wird.</string>
		<string lang="en">$fire$ can be extinguished by applying $cooldown$ or $outoforder$ to the module.</string>
        <string lang="fr">$fire$ peut être éteint en infligeant le module sur $cooldown$ ou $outoforder$.</string>
        <string lang="zh">通过让模块进入$cooldown$或$outoforder$状态，可以熄灭$fire$。</string>
        <string lang="jp">$fire$は、$cooldown$や$outoforder$の状態にすることで消火できる。</string>
        <string lang="ru">$fire$ можно потушить, накладывая на модуль состояние $cooldown$ или $outoforder$.</string>
        <string lang="es">$fire$ puede ser extinguido infligiendo el módulo en $cooldown$ o $outoforder$.</string>
        <string lang="kr">$fire$는 $cooldown$ 또는 $outoforder$ 상태의 모듈로 만들어 끌 수 있습니다.</string>
        <string lang="pt-br">$fire$ pode ser extinto infligindo o módulo em $cooldown$ ou $outoforder$.</string>
        <string lang="zh-tw">通過讓模組進入$cooldown$或$outoforder$狀態，可以熄滅$fire$。
</string>
        <string lang="uk">$fire$ можна загасити, накладаючи на модуль стан $cooldown$ або $outoforder$.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-happenings">
		<string lang="de">$b$?$/b$-Ereignisse bieten die Möglichkeit, deine Module zu duplizieren, zu transformieren oder zu verbessern.</string>
		<string lang="en">$b$?$/b$-Levels offer options to duplicate, transform or improve your modules.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Les événements $b$?$/b$ offrent des options pour dupliquer, transformer ou améliorer vos modules.</string>
		<string lang="zh">$b$？$/b$-关卡提供复制、转换或改进模块的机会。</string>
		<string lang="jp">$b$？$/b$面では、モジュールの複製、変換、$br$または改良の選択肢が提示される。</string>
		<string lang="ru">События $b$?$/b$ предлагают варианты дублирования, преобразования или улучшения ваших модулей.</string>
		<string lang="es">Los eventos $b$?$/b$ ofrecen opciones para duplicar, transformar o mejorar tus módulos.</string>
		<string lang="kr">$b$?$/b$-레벨은 모듈을 복제, 변형, 개선시킬 수 있는 선택지를 제공합니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Os eventos $b$?$/b$ oferecem opções para duplicar, transformar ou melhorar seus módulos.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">$b$？$/b$-關卡提供複製、轉換或改進模組的機會。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">$b$?$/b$- Рівні пропонують варіанти дублювання, трансформації або покращення модулів.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-middleclick">
		<string lang="de">Wenn du mit Tastatur und Maus spielst, kannst du mit einem Mittelklick auf ein Modul es in den Rucksack verschieben und wieder herausnehmen.</string>
		<string lang="en">When playing with keyboard and mouse, middle-clicking on a module will send it in and out of the backpack.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Lorsque vous jouez avec le clavier et la souris, un clic du milieu sur un module l'enverra dans et hors du sac à dos.</string>
		<string lang="zh">使用键盘鼠标游戏时，中键单击模块可将其快速移至背包。</string>
		<string lang="jp">キーボードとマウスでプレイする場合、$br$モジュールを中クリックでバックパックに出し入れできる。</string>
		<string lang="ru">При игре с клавиатурой и мышью, средний щелчок мыши по модулю отправит его в рюкзак и обратно.</string>
		<string lang="es">Cuando juegas con teclado y ratón, hacer clic con el botón central en un módulo lo enviará dentro y fuera de la mochila.</string>
		<string lang="kr">키보드와 마우스로 플레이 시, 가운데 클릭을 통해 모듈을 배낭으로 바로 넣거나 꺼낼 수 있습니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Ao jogar com teclado e mouse, clicar com o botão do meio em um módulo o enviará para dentro e para fora da mochila.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">使用鍵盤滑鼠遊戲時，中鍵單擊模組可將其快速移至背包。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Під час гри з клавіатурою та мишею, можна клацнути середньою кнопкою миші на модулі, щоб відправити його до рюкзаку або назад з рюкзака.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-negativeplasma">
        <string lang="de">Du kannst einen bewusstlosen Charakter vom Loot-Bildschirm aus wiederbeleben, anstatt ein Loot-Modul auszuwählen. Dein $plasma$ kann dabei ins Negative gehen.</string>
		<string lang="en">You can revive an unconscious character from the loot screen instead of picking a loot module. Your $plasma$ can go into the negative like this.</string>
        <string lang="fr">Vous pouvez réanimer un personnage inconscient à partir de l'écran de butin au lieu de choisir un module de butin. Votre $plasma$ peut devenir négatif de cette manière.</string>
        <string lang="zh">你可以从战利品界面复活一个昏迷的角色，而不是选择一个战利品模块。这样你的$plasma$可能会变成负数。</string>
        <string lang="jp">戦利品画面から戦利品モジュールを選ぶ代わりに、$br$意識不明のキャラクターを蘇生することができます。$br$このようにして$plasma$がマイナスになることがあります。</string>
        <string lang="ru">Вы можете оживить без сознания персонажа с экрана добычи вместо выбора модуля добычи. Ваш $plasma$ может стать отрицательным.</string>
        <string lang="es">Puedes revivir a un personaje inconsciente desde la pantalla de botín en lugar de elegir un módulo de botín. Tu $plasma$ puede volverse negativo de esta manera.</string>
        <string lang="kr">전리품 화면에서 전리품 모듈을 선택하는 대신, 의식을 잃은 캐릭터를 부활시킬 수 있습니다. 이렇게 하면 $plasma$가 마이너스가 될 수 있습니다.</string>
        <string lang="pt-br">Você pode reviver um personagem inconsciente na tela de saque em vez de escolher um módulo de saque. Seu $plasma$ pode ficar negativo dessa forma.</string>
        <string lang="zh-tw">你可以從戰利品畫面復活一個昏迷的角色，而不是選擇一個戰利品模組。這樣你的$plasma$可能會變成負數。
</string>
        <string lang="uk">Ви можете оживити без свідомості персонажа з екрану добутку замість вибору модуля добутку. Ваш $plasma$ може стати від'ємним.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-rating">
		<string lang="de">Wenn du eine $special$-Bewertung erhältst wird die Dauer für $special$ im nächsten Kampf um 2 reduziert.</string>
		<string lang="en">If you receive a $special$ rating, the duration for $special$ in the next fight will be reduced by 2.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Si vous obtenez une note $special$, la durée de la note $special$ dans le prochain combat sera réduite de 2.</string>
		<string lang="zh">如果本关取得$special$评分，则下一次战斗的$special$评分将缩短2步。</string>
		<string lang="jp">$special$評価を獲得すると、$br$次の戦闘で$special$の猶予時間が2縮む。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Если вы получите оценку $special$, продолжительность оценки $special$ в следующей схватке будет сокращена на 2.</string>
		<string lang="es">Si recibes una calificación $special$, la duración de la calificación $special$ en la siguiente pelea se reducirá en 2.</string>
		<string lang="kr">$special$ 등급을 획득했다면, 다음 전투에서 $special$를 획득할 수 있는 기간이 2 감소합니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Se você receber uma classificação $special$, a duração da classificação $special$ na próxima luta será reduzida em 2.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">如果本關取得$special$評分，則下一次戰鬥的$special$評分將縮短2步。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Отримання $special$ рейтингу зменшує термін для взяття $special$ у наступному бою на 2.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-rating-2">
		<string lang="de">Nicht alle Kämpfe können mit einer $special$-Belohnung abgeschlossen werden. In diesen Fällen kannst du dir mehr Zeit nehmen, um dich zu heilen und Plasma und Ressourcen für zukünftige Kämpfe zu generieren.</string>
		<string lang="en">Not all battles can be completed in time for a $special$ rating. In these cases, consider taking extra time to heal up and generate plasma and resources for future fights.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Tous les combats ne peuvent pas être terminés à temps pour une récompense $special$. Dans ces cas, envisagez de prendre plus de temps pour vous soigner et générer du plasma et des ressources pour les futurs combats.</string>
		<string lang="zh">并非所有战斗都能快速结束以取得$special$评分。这时不妨多花些时间治疗自己，并为之后的战斗产出等离子体及其他资源。</string>
		<string lang="jp">全ての戦闘で$special$評価を時間内に獲得できるとは限らない。その場合、余った時間をプラズマやリソースの生成に費やし、$br$将来の戦いに備えよう。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Не все бои можно завершить вовремя для получения награды $special$. В этих случаях рассмотрите возможность потратить дополнительное время на лечение и на генерацию плазмы и ресурсов для будущих сражений.</string>
		<string lang="es">No todas las batallas se pueden completar a tiempo para obtener una recompensa $special$. En estos casos, considera tomarte un tiempo extra para curarte y generar plasma y recursos para futuras peleas.</string>
		<string lang="kr">모든 전투를 $special$ 등급으로 마무리할 수 있는 건 아닙니다. 이럴 때는 향후 전투를 대비해, 시간을 추가로 사용해 체력을 치유하거나 플라즈마나 자원을 생성하는 것을 고려해보세요.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Nem todas as batalhas podem ser concluídas a tempo para uma classificação $special$. Nesses casos, considere tirar um tempo extra para se curar e gerar plasma e recursos para lutas futuras.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">並非所有戰鬥都能快速結束以取得$special$評分。這時不妨多花些時間治療自己，並為之後的戰鬥產出等離子體及其他資源。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Не кожен бій можна встигнути завершити з $special$ рейтингом. В такому разі можна використати додатковий час для лікування та генерації плазми і ресурсів для майбутніх боїв.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-rerolling">
		<string lang="de">Wenn dir keines der drei Loot-Module zusagt, kannst du $plasma$ ausgeben, um den Loot neu auszuwürfeln. Dies ändert nicht dessen Seltenheit.</string>
		<string lang="en">If no loot module does it for you, you can spend $plasma$ to reroll.$br$This will not change the rarity of the loot.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Si aucun module de butin ne vous convient, vous pouvez dépenser du $plasma$ pour renouveler les modules. Cela ne changera pas leurs rareté.</string>
		<string lang="zh">如果没有心仪的战利品模块，可以花费$plasma$重新选择。重选不会改变战利品的稀有度等级。</string>
		<string lang="jp">戦利品のモジュールにほしいものがなければ、$br$$plasma$消費でリロールできる。$br$リロールしても、戦利品のレアリティは変わらない。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Если ни один модуль добычи не подходит вам, вы можете потратить плазму, чтобы перебросить. Это не изменит редкость добычи.</string>
		<string lang="es">Si ningún módulo del botín te sirve, puedes gastar $plasma$ para volver a tirar. Esto no cambiará la rareza del botín.</string>
		<string lang="kr">마음에 드는 전리품 모듈이 없다면, $plasma$를 지불해 새로고침을 할 수 있습니다. 전리품의 희귀도는 변경되지 않습니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Se nenhum módulo de saque fizer isso por você, você pode gastar $plasma$ para rolar novamente. Isso não mudará a raridade do saque.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">如果沒有心儀的戰利品模組，可以花費$plasma$重新選擇。重選不會改變戰利品的稀有度等級。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Якщо нічого зі здобичі тобі не підходить, її можна оновити, витративши $plasmaicon$$b$Плазму$/b$.$br$Це не змінить рідкості модулів.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-rightclick">
		<string lang="de">Wenn du mit Tastatur und Maus spielst, kannst du ein Modul mit einem Rechtsklick zum Rack des anderen Characters schicken.</string>
		<string lang="en">When playing with keyboard and mouse, right-clicking on a module will send it to the other character's rack.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Lorsque vous jouez avec le clavier et la souris, un clic droit sur un module l'enverra dans le rack de l'autre personnage.</string>
		<string lang="zh">使用键盘鼠标游戏时，右键单击模块可将其快速移至另一角色的模架。</string>
		<string lang="jp">キーボードとマウスでプレイする場合、$br$モジュールを右クリックで$br$別キャラクターのラックに移せる。</string>
		<string lang="ru">При игре с клавиатурой и мышью, щелчок правой кнопкой мыши по модулю отправит его в стойку другого персонажа.</string>
		<string lang="es">Cuando juegas con teclado y ratón, hacer clic derecho en un módulo lo enviará al bastidor del otro personaje.</string>
		<string lang="kr">키보드와 마우스로 플레이 시, 오른쪽 클릭을 통해 모듈을 다른 캐릭터의 랙으로 보낼 수 있습니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Ao jogar com teclado e mouse, clicar com o botão direito em um módulo o enviará para o rack do outro personagem.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">使用鍵盤滑鼠遊戲時，右鍵單擊模組可將其快速移至另一角色的模架。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Під час гри за допомогою клавіатури та миші, можна клацанути правою кнопкою миші на модулі, щоб надіслати його до стійки іншого персонажа.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-salvage">
		<string lang="de">Wenn du Game Over gehst, vergiss nicht, dein bestes Modul in den nächsten Run hinüberzuretten.</string>
		<string lang="en">If you go Game Over, don't forget to salvage your best module$br$for the next run.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Si vous perdez, n'oubliez pas de récupérer votre meilleur module pour la prochaine partie.</string>
		<string lang="zh">如果游戏落败，别忘记保留你最爱的模块，以便下次游戏继承。</string>
		<string lang="jp">ゲームオーバーになった場合、$br$次のランに向けて最高のモジュールの回収を忘れずに。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Если вы проиграете, не забудьте спасти свой лучший модуль для следующего забега.</string>
		<string lang="es">Si pierdes la partida, no olvides salvar tu mejor módulo para el próximo intento.</string>
		<string lang="kr">게임 오버 시, 다음 모험을 위해 여러분이 지녔던 최고의 모듈들을 회수하는 걸 잊지 마세요.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Se você for Game Over, não se esqueça de salvar seu melhor módulo para a próxima rodada.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">如果遊戲落敗，別忘記保留你最愛的模組，以便下次遊戲繼承。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Якщо ти програв, не забудь врятувати свій найкращий модуль для наступного походу.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-storm">
		<string lang="de">Wenn du einen Kampf nicht rechtzeitig beendest, zieht ein $storm$ auf und der Kampf nimmt eine gefährliche Wendung.</string>
		<string lang="en">If you can't manage to end a battle in time, a $storm$ is gathering and the battle will take a dangerous turn.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Si vous ne parvenez pas à mettre fin au combat à temps, une $storm$ se rassemble et la bataille prendra une tournure dangereuse.</string>
		<string lang="zh">如果未能及时结束战斗，将生成$storm$，战况会发生危险的转折。</string>
		<string lang="jp">戦闘を時間内に終わらせられなければ、$br$$storm$が発生し危険なターンが到来する可能性がある。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Если вы не сможете закончить бой вовремя, соберется $storm$ и битва примет опасный оборот.</string>
		<string lang="es">Si no puedes terminar la pelea a tiempo, se formará una $storm$ y la batalla tomará un giro peligroso.</string>
		<string lang="kr">시간 내에 전투를 끝내지 못한다면 $storm$이 몰려오게 되며, 전투는 위험한 방향으로 흘러갈 것입니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Se você não conseguir terminar a luta a tempo, uma $storm$ está se formando e a batalha tomará um rumo perigoso.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">如果未能及時結束戰鬥，將生成$storm$，戰況會發生危險的轉折。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Якщо не вийде завершити бій вчасно, збереться $storm$, і битва стане небезпечною.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-strategy">
		<string lang="de">Manche Kämpfe können dich mit gespawnten Monstern oder Status-Effekten überwältigen. Überlege dir sorgfältig, welche Ziele du priorisieren solltest.</string>
		<string lang="en">Some battles can overwhelm you with spawned monsters or debilitating status effects. Carefully consider your target priorities.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Certains combats peuvent vous submerger avec des monstres apparus ou des effets de statut débilitants. Considérez soigneusement vos priorités de cible.</string>
		<string lang="zh">一些战斗中出现的怪物数量或减益效果也许会令你应接不暇。请仔细考虑目标的优先级。</string>
		<string lang="jp">一部の戦闘では、増える怪物や状態異常で苦戦する恐れがある。$br$対象の優先順位に注意しよう。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Некоторые бои могут подавить вас с помощью появившихся монстров или ослабляющих статусных эффектов. Тщательно обдумайте приоритетные цели</string>
		<string lang="es">Algunas batallas pueden abrumarte con monstruos generados o efectos de estado debilitantes. Considera cuidadosamente la prioridad de tu objetivo.</string>
		<string lang="kr">일부 전투는 상대가 몬스터를 소환하거나 약화 효과로 인해 불리한 상태로 시작될 수도 있습니다. 목표 우선 순위를 신중하게 고려하세요.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Algumas batalhas podem sobrecarregá-lo com monstros gerados ou efeitos de status debilitantes. Considere cuidadosamente suas prioridades de alvo.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">一些戰鬥中出現的怪物數量或減益效果也許會令你應接不暇。請仔細考慮目標的優先順序。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Деякі битви можуть завалити тебе створеними монстрами або виснажливими статусними ефектами. Добре подумай над пріоритетами цілей.</string>
</set>
<set id="advice-timeline">
		<string lang="de">Zusätzliche Module, um die Zeitleiste zu manipulieren, sind äußerst nützlich für eine zuverlässigige Ausrichtung und Kontrolle der Züge.</string>
		<string lang="en">Additional modules to manipulate the timeline are very useful for reliable turn alignment and control.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Des modules supplémentaires impactant l'ordre chronologique sont très utiles pour se réaligner et contrôler l'ordonnancement des tours.</string>
		<string lang="zh">可操控时间轴的附加模块在轮次的对齐和控制上非常有用。</string>
		<string lang="jp">タイムラインを操作する追加モジュールは、$br$確実なターン制御に役立つ。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Дополнительные модули для манипулирования временной линией очень полезны для надежного выравнивания и контроля ходов.</string>
		<string lang="es">Los módulos adicionales para manipular la línea de tiempo son muy útiles para un alineamiento y control de turnos fiable.</string>
		<string lang="kr">타임라인을 조작할 수 있는 추가 모듈은 턴을 정렬하고 제어하는 데에 아주 유용하게 사용됩니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Módulos adicionais para manipular a linha do tempo são muito úteis para alinhamento e controle de turnos confiáveis.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">可操控時間軸的附加模組在輪次的對齊和控制上非常有用。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Модулі, що керують шкалою часу, стануть у нагоді для надійного вирівнювання ходів та контролю.</string>
</set>
</localization>
