<localization>
<set id="act">
		<string lang="de">Teil</string>
		<string lang="en">Part</string>
		<string lang="fr">Part</string>
		<string lang="zh">部分</string>
		<string lang="jp">アクト</string>
		<string lang="ru">Часть</string>
		<string lang="es">Parte</string>
		<string lang="kr">파트</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Parte</string>
</set>
<set id="act-1">
		<string lang="de">Teil I:</string>
		<string lang="en">Part I:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Part I:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第一部分</string>
		<string lang="jp">アクト1</string>
		<string lang="ru">Часть I:</string>
		<string lang="es">Parte I:</string>
		<string lang="kr">파트 I:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Parte I:</string>
</set>
<set id="act-2">
		<string lang="de">Teil II:</string>
		<string lang="en">Part II:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Part II:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第二部分</string>
		<string lang="jp">Part II:</string>
		<string lang="kr">파트 II:</string>
</set>
<set id="act-3">
		<string lang="de">Teil III:</string>
		<string lang="en">Part III:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Part III:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第三部分</string>
		<string lang="jp">Part III:</string>
		<string lang="kr">파트 III:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle1-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel I:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter I:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre I:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第一章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">チャプター1</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава I:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo I:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 I:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo I:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle1-story">
		<string lang="de">Es ist Getreidefest.$br$Nana Slopper war gerade dabei, einen gravioaktiven Truthahn in den Ofen zu schieben, als der Plasmazähler auf Null fiel.$br$Jemand sollte losziehen und erforschen, was den Ärger dieses Mal verursachte.</string>
		<string lang="en">It's grain festival.$br$Nana Slopper was about to put a gravioactive turkey in the oven when the plasma meter hit zero.$br$Someone should go and investigate what caused the ruckus this time.</string>
		<string lang="fr">C'est fête des céréales.$br$Mamie Slopper était sur le point de mettre une dinde gravioactive dans le four lorsque le compteur à plasma indique zéro.$br$Quelqu'un devrait aller $b$chercher du plasma$/b$ et étudier ce qui a causé la panne de ce fois-ci.</string>
		<string lang="zh">今天是谷物节。$br$斯洛普奶奶正要将引力火鸡塞进烤箱中，却发现等离子仪归零了。$br$该派人去查一查到底怎么回事。</string>
		<string lang="jp">穀物まつりです。$br$おばあちゃんスロッパーは、プラズマメーターがゼロになったとき、重力で活動する七面鳥をオーブンに入れようとしていました.$br$誰かがこの騒ぎの原因を調べに行かなければなりません。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Это фестиваль зерна.$br$Нана Слоппер собиралась положить гравиоактивную индейку в духовку, когда плазменный счетчик упал до нуля.$br$Кто-то должен пойти и выяснить, что вызвало проблемы на этот раз.</string>
		<string lang="es">Es el festival del grano.$br$Nana Slopper estaba a punto de poner un pavo gravioactivo en el horno cuando el medidor de plasma llegó a cero.$br$Alguien debería ir e investigar qué causó el alboroto esta vez.</string>
		<string lang="kr">곡물 잔치 기간입니다.$br$나나 슬로퍼가 중력 활성 칠면조를 오븐에 넣으려고 하기 직전에, 플라즈마 미터가 0을 기록했습니다.$br$이번 소동이 발생한 원인을 누군가 가서 조사해야만 합니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">É o festival do grão.$br$Nana Slopper estava prestes a colocar um peru gravioativo no forno quando o medidor de plasma atingiu zero.$br$Alguém deveria ir e investigar o que causou a confusão desta vez.</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle1-title">
		<string lang="de">Blackout</string>
		<string lang="en">Blackout</string>
		<string lang="fr">Blackout</string>
		<string lang="zh">断电</string>
		<string lang="jp">ブラックアウト</string>
		<string lang="ru">Блэкаут</string>
		<string lang="es">Apagón</string>
		<string lang="kr">암전</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Apagão</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle2-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel II:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter II:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre II:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第二章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">チャプター2</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава II:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo II:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 II:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo II:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle2-story">
		<string lang="de">“Der Gyrograph ist völlig am durchdrehen. Und schaut euch mein Frühstück an! Das Rührei hat sich entrührt!$br$Wenn wir nicht verstehen, was die Zeitverzerrungen verursacht, riskieren wir, selbst … entrührt … zu werden.”</string>
		<string lang="en">“The gyrograph is all over the place. And look at my breakfast! These eggs have unscrambled themselves!$br$If we don’t understand what’s causing the time distortions we risk getting … unscrambled … too.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">“Le gyrographe est complètement détraqué. Et regardez mon petit-déjeuner! Les œufs se sont déscramblés!$br$Si nous ne comprenons pas ce qui cause les distorsions temporelles, nous risquons de nous faire … déscrambler … aussi.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">“到处都是漩涡。看看我的早餐！这些鸡蛋全都乱码了！$br$如果不尽快搞清楚造成时间扭曲的原因，我们很有可能……也会……变成乱码。”</string>
		<string lang="jp">“ジャイログラフは完全に狂っています。そして私の朝食を見てください！これらの卵は自分で解きほぐされました！$br$時間の歪みを引き起こしているものがわからなければ、私たちは……自分で解きほぐされる……危険があります。”</string>
		<string lang="ru">“Гирограф полностью вышел из строя. И посмотрите на мой завтрак! Эти яйца размешались сами!$br$Если мы не поймем, что вызывает временные искажения, мы рискуем сами … размешаться … тоже.”</string>
		<string lang="es">“El giroscopio está completamente descontrolado. ¡Y mira mi desayuno! ¡Estos huevos se han desrevuelto ellos solos!$br$Si no entendemos qué está causando las distorsiones temporales, corremos el riesgo de … desrevolvernos … también.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">“자이로그래프가 사방에 널려있어요. 그리고 제 아침 좀 봐요! 계란들이 멋대로 원래대로 돌아가고 있잖아요!$br$시간 왜곡의 원인을 정확히 파악하지 못하면 어쩌면 우리도...원래대로...돌아가버릴 거에요.”</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle2-title">
		<string lang="de">Verdrehte Logik</string>
		<string lang="en">Scrambled Logic</string>
		<string lang="fr">Logique Tordue</string>
		<string lang="zh">时空干扰</string>
		<string lang="jp">混乱したロジック</string>
		<string lang="ru">Перемешанная логика</string>
		<string lang="es">Lógica Revuelta</string>
		<string lang="kr">뒤죽박죽 논리</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Lógica Embaralhada</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle3-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel III:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter III:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre III:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第三章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">チャプター3</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава III:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo III:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 III:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo III:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle3-story">
		<string lang="de">“Lange Zeit gab es Gerüchte von Leuten, die unsere Zeit stehlen. Niemand hat damals zugehört, und jetzt schau dir alles an! Du hast sicher auch Leute verloren. Ich kann nicht ruhen, bis ich die Verantwortlichen gefunden habe.”</string>
		<string lang="en">“For a long time there were rumours of people stealing our time. Nobody listened back then, and now look at everything! You must have lost people too. I can't rest until I've found those responsible.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">“Pendant longtemps, il y a eu des rumeurs de gens volant notre temps. Personne n'écoutait à l'époque, et maintenant regardez tout! Vous avez sûrement aussi perdu des gens. Je ne peux pas me reposer tant que je n'ai pas trouvé les responsables.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">“很长一段时间都有传言说，有人偷走了我们的时间。没人相信这种鬼话，但现在看看这一切！你一定也失去过至亲至爱。不找到凶手我决不罢休！”</string>
		<string lang="jp">“長い間、私たちの時間を盗む人々の噂がありました。当時誰も聞いてくれませんでしたが、今はすべてを見てください！あなたもきっと人を失ったでしょう。私は責任者を見つけるまで安心できません。”</string>
		<string lang="ru">“Долгое время ходили слухи, что люди крадут наше время. Тогда никто не слушал, а теперь посмотрите на все! Вы наверняка тоже потеряли людей. Я не могу успокоиться, пока не найду виновных.”</string>
		<string lang="es">“Durante mucho tiempo hubo rumores de personas que nos robaban el tiempo. Nadie escuchó en aquel entonces, y ahora mira todo ésto! Seguro que tú también has perdido gente. No puedo descansar hasta que encuentre a los responsables.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">“아주 오랜 시간 동안, 우리의 시간을 훔쳐가는 사람들에 관한 수많은 소문이 있었죠. 그땐 아무도 주의 깊게 듣지 않았지만, 이 꼴 좀 보세요! 당신도 누군가를 잃었나보군요. 관련된 자들을 찾기 전까진 쉴 수 없을 것 같습니다.”</string>>
</set>
<set id="cycle3-title">
		<string lang="de">Zeitverschwendung</string>
		<string lang="en">A Waste of Time</string>
		<string lang="fr">Perte de Temps</string>
		<string lang="zh">浪费时间</string>
		<string lang="jp">時間の無駄遣い</string>
		<string lang="ru">Потеря времени</string>
		<string lang="es">Pérdida de Tiempo</string>
		<string lang="kr">시간 낭비</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Perda de Tempo</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle4-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel IV:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter IV:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre IV:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第四章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">チャプター4</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава IV:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo IV:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 IV:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo IV:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle4-story">
		<string lang="de">“Die ersten Jahre der Gravitonikforschung waren schrecklich ereignislos. Wir verbrachten Jahre damit, zu berechnen, wie sich mit Zeitdilatation das menschliche Leben verlängern lässt.$br$Die Theorie war solide, aber es bestand die Gefahr einer katastrophalen Zeitschwemme.”$br$– “Was ist dann passiert?”$br$“Das Projekt wurde plötzlich eingestellt und alle wurden rausgeschmissen”</string>
		<string lang="en">“The first years of gravitonics research were terribly uneventful. We spent years calculating the potential of time dilation to prolong human life. The theory was sound, but there was a risk of catastrophic time spillage onto the environment.”$br$– “What happened then?”$br$“The project went dark and everybody got kicked off.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">“Les premières années de la recherche en gravitonique étaient terriblement ennuyeuses. Nous avons passé des années à calculer le potentiel de la dilatation du temps pour prolonger la vie humaine.$br$La théorie était solide, mais il y avait un risque de déversement temporel catastrophique dans l'environnement.”$br$– “Qu'est-il arrivé ensuite?”$br$“Le projet a été arrêté brusquement et tout le monde a été viré.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">“引力研究之初一切风平浪静。我们花了数年时间计算通过时间膨胀来延长人类寿命的可能性。理论上是可行的，但伴随的风险，时间溢出对环境的影响，也是灾难性的。”$br$–“后来呢？”$br$“项目中断，所有人被踢了出来。”</string>
		<string lang="jp">“重力学研究の最初の数年間は非常に退屈でした。私たちは数年間、時間の膨張が人間の寿命を延ばす可能性を計算しました。理論は確かでしたが、環境に対する時間の大量流出のリスクがありました。”$br$– “その後どうなりましたか？”$br$“プロジェクトは突然停止し、誰もが追い出されました。”</string>
		<string lang="ru">“Первые годы исследований гравитоники были ужасно скучными. Мы потратили годы на расчет потенциала временного растяжения для продления человеческой жизни. Теория была звучной, но существовала опасность катастрофического временного разлива в окружающую среду.”$br$– “Что случилось потом?”$br$“Проект внезапно остановился, и всех выгнали.”</string>
		<string lang="es">“Los primeros años de la investigación gravitonica fueron terriblemente aburridos. Pasamos años calculando el potencial de la dilatación del tiempo para prolongar la vida humana. La teoría era sólida, pero existía el riesgo de un derrame temporal catastrófico en el medio ambiente.”$br$– “¿Qué pasó entonces?”$br$“El proyecto se detuvo de repente y todos fueron despedidos.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">“처음 중력학 연구를 시작한 해에는 딱히 별다른 일이 없었어. 인간의 생명을 연장시킬 시간 팽창의 가능성을 계산하는 데에 몇 년을 소비했지. 이론은 논리적으로 타당했지만, 주변에 대규모 시간 유출이 발생할 위험성이 있었어.”$br$–“그리고 무슨 일이 일어났죠?”$br$“프로젝트는 중단됐고 모든 사람들이 쫓겨났지.”</string>>
</set>
<set id="cycle4-title">
		<string lang="de">Ebbe und Flut</string>
		<string lang="en">Ebb and Flow</string>
		<string lang="fr">Basse et Haute</string>
		<string lang="zh">潮起潮落</string>
		<string lang="jp">満ち潮と引き潮</string>
		<string lang="ru">Прилив и отлив</string>
		<string lang="es">Flujo y Reflujo</string>
		<string lang="kr">밀물과 썰물</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle5-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel V:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter V:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre V:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第五章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">チャプター5</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава V:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo V:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 V:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo V:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle5-story">
		<string lang="de">“Das Wesen einer Falte besteht in einem Knick und einer Verdoppelung.”$br$– “Sind wir uns schon einmal begegnet?”$br$“Es gibt nicht so etwas wie ‚schon‘. Noch gibt es so etwas wie ‚einmal‘. Wir begegnen uns jetzt. Wir werden uns immer jetzt begegnen. Und ich werde dir immer sagen, dass du dich von diesem Ort fernhalten sollst. Das ist der Knick. Und morgen wirst du auf dem Weg sein.”</string>
		<string lang="en">“The nature of a fold is that of a doubling and a crease.”$br$– “Have we met before?”$br$“There is no such thing as before. Nor after. We are meeting now. We will always be meeting now. And I will always be telling you to stay away from that place. This is the crease. And tomorrow you will be on your way.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">“La nature d'un pli est celle d'un doublement et d'une arête.”$br$– “Nous nous sommes déjà rencontrés?”$br$“Il n'y a pas de tel chose que ‚déjà‘. Nous nous rencontrons maintenant. Nous nous toujours rencontrerons maintenant. Et je vous toujours dirai de rester loin de cet endroit. Ceci est l'arête. Et demain, vous serez en route.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">“折叠的本质，是重合加折痕。”$br$“我们以前见过吗？”$br$“不存在所谓的‘以前’。同理没有以后。我们只在此刻相遇。我们永远会在此刻相遇。每一次我都会告诉你不要去那个地方。这就是折痕。而明天你会再次踏上你的征途。”</string>
		<string lang="jp">“折り目の性質は、二重と折り目です。”$br$– “私たちは以前会ったことがありますか？”$br$“以前というものはありません。また、後にもありません。私たちは今会っています。私たちはいつも今会っています。そして私はいつもあなたにその場所から離れるように言います。これが折り目です。明日、あなたは途中にいるでしょう。”</string>
		<string lang="ru">“Природа складки заключается в удвоении и складке.”$br$– “Мы встречались раньше?”$br$“Такого понятия, как ‚раньше‘, не существует. Ни ‚позже‘. Мы встречаемся сейчас. Мы всегда будем встречаться сейчас. И я всегда буду говорить тебе держаться подальше от этого места. Это складка. А завтра ты будешь в пути.”</string>
		<string lang="es">“La naturaleza de un pliegue es la de un doblez de una arruga.”$br$– “¿Nos hemos conocido antes?”$br$“No hay tal cosa como antes. Ni después. Nos estamos conociendo ahora. Siempre nos estaremos conociendo ahora. Y siempre te diré que te mantengas alejado de ese lugar. Ésto es la arruga. Y mañana estarás de camino.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">“접는 행위의 본질은, 두 배가 되고 주름이 생긴다는 것입니다.”$br$–“우리 전에 만난 적 있나요?”$br$“전 같은 건 존재하지 않습니다. 이후도 없죠. 우린 지금 만나고 있는 겁니다. 우린 항상 지금 만나게 될 겁니다. 그리고 난 항상 당신에게 그곳에서 멀리 떨어져 있으라고 말하겠죠. 이게 주름이에요. 내일이면 당신은 제 갈 길을 떠날겁니다.”</string>>
		<string lang="pt-br">“A natureza de uma prega é a de um dobramento e uma ruga.”$br$– “Nós já nos conhecemos antes?”$br$“Não há tal coisa como antes. Nem depois. Estamos nos conhecendo agora. Estaremos sempre nos conhecendo agora. E eu sempre estarei dizendo para você ficar longe daquele lugar. Esta é a ruga. E amanhã você estará a caminho.”</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle5-title">
		<string lang="de">Entfaltung</string>
		<string lang="en">Unfolding</string>
		<string lang="fr">Déploiement</string>
		<string lang="zh">展开</string>
		<string lang="jp">展開</string>
		<string lang="ru">Разворачивание</string>
		<string lang="es">Despliegue</string>
		<string lang="kr">펼치기</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Desdobramento</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle6-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel VI:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter VI:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre VI:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第六章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">チャプター6</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава VI:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo VI:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 VI:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo VI:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle6-story">
		<string lang="de">“Wenn ihr diese Nachricht hört, bedeutet es, dass etwas furchtbar schief gelaufen ist.”$br$– “Das ist Opa Sloppers Stimme!”$br$“Sie bauen eine schwebende Stadt, um die sie einen Damm errichten, der den Fluss der Zeit stoppt. Sie tauften sie Eden. Sie waren nicht sehr kreativ.$br$Ich muss das letzte Axiom der Gravitonik sicher verstecken, und zwar bei der Person, die am wenigsten wahrscheinlich mit hineingezogen wird.”</string>
		<string lang="en">“If you're hearing this message, it means that things have gone terribly wrong.”$br$– “It’s Grandpa Slopper’s voice!”$br$“They’re building a floating city, around which they're constructing a dam to halt the flow of time. They called it Eden. They weren’t very creative.$br$I have to hide the last axiom of gravitonics with the person least likely to become involved.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">“Si vous entendez ce message, cela signifie que les choses ont terriblement mal tourné.”$br$– “C'est la voix de Papi Slopper!”$br$“Ils construisent une ville flottante, autour de laquelle ils construisent un barrage pour arrêter le flux du temps. Ils l'ont appelée Eden. Ils n'étaient pas très créatifs.$br$Je dois cacher le dernier axiome de la gravitonique avec la personne la moins susceptible de s'impliquer.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">“如果你收到这条消息，就意味着形势已经相当危急了。”$br$“是斯洛普爷爷的声音！”$br$“它们正在建造一座浮空的城市，并在其周围修建了一圈大坝来阻止时间的流动。他们称之为伊甸园。很没有新意的名字。$br$我必须把引力学的最后一条公理藏到最不可能卷入其中的人身上。”</string>
		<string lang="jp">“もしこのメッセージを聞いているなら、事態がひどく悪化していることを意味します。”$br$– “それはスロッパーおじいちゃんの声です！”$br$“彼らは時間の流れを止めるために浮遊都市を建設しています。彼らはそれをエデンと呼んでいます。彼らはあまり創造的ではありませんでした。$br$私は重力学の最後の公理を最も関与しない人に隠さなければなりません。”</string>
		<string lang="ru">“Если вы слышите это сообщение, это означает, что что-то пошло ужасно не так.”$br$– “Это голос дедушки Слоппера!”$br$“Они строят плавающий город, вокруг которого они строят плотину, чтобы остановить поток времени. Они назвали его Эден. Они не были очень креативны.$br$Мне нужно спрятать последний аксиом гравитоники у человека, который меньше всего вероя</string>
		<string lang="es">“Si estás escuchando este mensaje, significa que las cosas han salido terriblemente mal.”$br$– “¡Es la voz del abuelo Slopper!”$br$“Están construyendo una ciudad flotante, alrededor de la cual están construyendo un dique para detener el flujo del tiempo. La llamaron Edén. No fueron muy creativos.$br$Debo esconder el último axioma de la gravitónica con la persona menos susceptible a involucrarse.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">“만약 이 메시지를 듣고 있다면, 상황이 굉장히 좋지 않게 돌아가고 있다는 뜻이겠구만.”$br$– “슬로퍼 할아버지 목소리야!”$br$“그 자들이 공중 도시를 건설하고, 시간의 흐름을 막기 위해 댐을 만들었어. 에덴이라고 부르더군. 창의력하고는.$br$나는 연관될 가능성이 가장 적은 사람에게, 중력학의 마지막 원리를 남겨야 한다.”</string>>
		<string lang="pt-br">“Se você está ouvindo esta mensagem, significa que as coisas deram terrivelmente errado.”$br$– “É a voz do vovô Slopper!”$br$“Eles estão construindo uma cidade flutuante, em torno da qual estão construindo uma barragem para interromper o fluxo do tempo. Eles a chamaram de Éden. Eles não foram muito criativos.$br$Tenho que esconder o último axioma da gravitonica com a pessoa menos provável de se envolver.”</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle6-title">
		<string lang="de">Eine Stadt in den Wolken</string>
		<string lang="en">A City in the Skies</string>
		<string lang="fr">Une Ville dans les Cieux</string>
		<string lang="zh">浮空之城</string>
		<string lang="jp">空の都市</string>
		<string lang="ru">Город в небесах</string>
		<string lang="es">Una Ciudad en los Cielos</string>
		<string lang="kr">하늘 위의 도시</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Uma Cidade nos Céus</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle7-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel VII:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter VII:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre VII:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第七章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">チャプター7</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава VII:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo VII:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 VII:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo VII:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle7-story">
		<string lang="de">“Entschuldigung, dass wir deinen Holo-Stream unterbrechen, Jessy, aber wir glauben, dass der Schlüssel zur Rettung der Welt irgendwo in deinem Kopf gespeichert sein könnte.”$br$– “Ähh … nö.”$br$“Jess! Was hat Opa dir als Letztes gesagt, bevor er verschwunden ist?”$br$– “Keine Ahnung … irgendwas mit Rosen und Veilchen und dass die zeitliche Masse umgekehrt proportional zur gravitonischen Energie zum Quadrat ist.”</string>
		<string lang="en">“Sorry to interrupt your holo-stream, Jessy, but we believe the key to saving the world might be stored somewhere in your mind.”$br$– “Yeah … no.”$br$“Jess! What’s the last thing Grandpa said to you?”$br$– “Dunno … something about roses and violets and the temporal mass being inversely proportional to the gravitonic energy squared.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">“Désolé d'interrompre votre holo-streaming, Jessy, mais nous croyons que la clé pour sauver le monde pourrait être stockée quelque part dans ta tête.”$br$– “Euh … non.”$br$“Jess! Qu'est-ce que Papi t'a dit la dernière fois?”$br$– “Je sais pas … quelque chose à propos de roses et de violettes et que la masse temporelle est inversement proportionnelle à l'énergie gravitonique au carré.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">“抱歉打扰了你的全息直播，杰西，但我们有理由相信拯救世界的关键，就藏在你脑海中的某处。”$br$– “呃……并没有。”$br$“杰西！想想爷爷最后跟你说了什么？”$br$– “我不确……什么玫瑰和紫罗兰，还有时间质量和引力能量的平方成反比什么的。”</string>
		<string lang="jp">“ホロ・ストリームを中断してすみません、ジェシー、でも私たちは世界を救う鍵があなたの頭のどこかに保存されているかもしれないと信じています。”$br$– “うん……違う。”$br$“ジェシー！おじいちゃんが最後にあなたに言ったことは何ですか？”$br$– “わからない……バラとスミレについて、時間質量が重力エネルギーの二乗に反比例することについて。”</string>
		<string lang="ru">“Извините, что мы прерываем ваш голо-поток, Джесси, но мы считаем, что ключ к спасению мира может быть где-то в вашем разуме.”$br$– “Да … нет.”$br$“Джесс! Что последнее сказал тебе дедушка?”$br$– “Не знаю … что-то о розах и фиалках и о том, что временная масса обратно пропорциональна квадрату гравитонной энергии.”</string>
		<string lang="es">“Disculpa interrumpir tu holo-stream, Jessy, pero creemos que la clave para salvar el mundo podría estar almacenada en algún lugar de tu mente.”$br$– “Sí … no.”$br$“¡Jess! ¿Qué fue lo último que te dijo el abuelo?”$br$– “No sé … algo sobre rosas y violetas y que la masa temporal es inversamente proporcional al cuadrado de la energía gravitónica.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">“홀로스트림을 방해해서 미안하지만, 제시, 우린 세상을 구할 열쇠가 너의 머릿속에 있다고 믿는다.”$br$–“어...아뇨.”$br$“제스! 할아버지가 마지막으로 너한테 남기신 말이 뭐지?”$br$–“몰라요...그냥 장미랑 제비꽃에 관한 얘기랑 시간 질량은 중력 에너지 제곱에 반비례한다고 하셨어요.”</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">“Desculpe interromper seu holo-stream, Jessy, mas acreditamos que a chave para salvar o mundo pode estar armazenada em algum lugar de sua mente.”$br$– “Sim … não.”$br$“Jess! O que foi a última coisa que o vovô disse para você?”$br$– “Não sei … algo sobre rosas e violetas e que a massa temporal é inversamente proporcional ao quadrado da energia gravitônica.”</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle7-title">
		<string lang="de">Veilchen sind Blau</string>
		<string lang="en">Violets are Blue</string>
		<string lang="fr">Les Violettes sont Bleues</string>
		<string lang="zh">蓝色的紫罗兰</string>
		<string lang="jp">スミレは青い</string>
		<string lang="ru">Фиалки синие</string>
		<string lang="es">Las Violetas son Azules</string>
		<string lang="kr">제비꽃은 푸르다</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Violetas são Azuis</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle8-description">
		<string lang="de">Letztes Kapitel:</string>
		<string lang="en">Final Chapter:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Dernier Chapitre:</string>
		<string lang="zh">终章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">最終章:</string>
		<string lang="ru">Последняя глава:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo Final:</string>
		<string lang="kr">마지막 챕터:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo Final:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle8-story">
		<string lang="de">“Sie wissen genau, welchen Schaden sie anrichten. Aber in ihrer Gier wollen sie in einem unendlichen Tag schwelgen.$br$Der Zeitdamm wird von einer einzigen Energiequelle angetrieben: dem Grav-Reaktor.”$br$– “Wie weißt du das alles?”$br$“Weil ich von dort komme.”</string>
		<string lang="en">“They know exactly about the damage they are causing. But in their greed, they want to revel in an infinite day.$br$ The time dam is powered by a single source of power: the grav reactor.”$br$– “How do you know all this?”$br$“Because I am from there.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">“Ils savent exactement les dégâts qu'ils causent. Mais dans leur avidité, ils veulent se délecter d'un jour infini.$br$Le barrage temporel est alimenté par une seule source d'énergie: le réacteur gravitationnel.”$br$– “Comment sais-tu tout ça?”$br$“Parce que je viens de là-bas.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">“他们对自己造成的破坏一清二楚。但因为贪婪，他们仍然想纵情享受无限的一天。$br$时间大坝的能量来源只有一个：引力反应堆。”$br$– “你怎么知道的？”$br$“因为我就来自那里。”</string>
		<string lang="jp">“彼らは自分たちが引き起こしている損害について正確に知っています。しかし、彼らの欲望の中で、彼らは無限の日に浸りたいと思っています。$br$時間ダムは単一のエネルギー源で駆動されています: 重力反応炉。”$br$– “あなたはこれらすべてをどうやって知っているのですか？”$br$“なぜなら私はそこから来ているからです。”</string>
		<string lang="ru">“Они точно знают о вреде, который они наносят. Но в своей жадности они хотят наслаждаться бесконечным днем.$br$Временной дам приводится в действие единственным источником энергии: гравитационным реактором.”$br$– “Откуда ты все это знаешь?”$br$“Потому что я оттуда.”</string>
		<string lang="es">“Ellos saben exactamente el daño que están causando. Pero en su codicia, quieren deleitarse en un día infinito.$br$La presa del tiempo es alimentada por una única fuente de energía: el reactor gravitatorio.”$br$– “¿Cómo sabes todo esto?”$br$“Porque soy de allí.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">“그 자식들은 자기들이 무슨 피해를 끼치고 있는지 정확히 알고 있어. 하지만 탐욕스럽게 무한한 매일을 지내고 싶어하는 거지.$br$시간 댐의 동력원은 딱 하나야: 중력 원자로.”$br$–“그걸 어떻게 다 알고 계시는 거죠?”$br$“내가 거기에서 왔거든.”</string>>
		<string lang="pt-br">“Eles sabem exatamente sobre o dano que estão causando. Mas em sua ganância, eles querem se deleitar em um dia infinito.$br$A barragem do tempo é alimentada por uma única fonte de energia: o reator gravitacional.”$br$– “Como você sabe de tudo isso?”$br$“Porque eu sou de lá.”</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle8-title">
		<string lang="de">Der Ummauerte Garten</string>
		<string lang="en">The Walled Garden</string>
		<string lang="fr">Le Jardin Enclos</string>
		<string lang="zh">围墙内的伊甸园</string>
		<string lang="jp">囲まれた庭</string>
		<string lang="ru">Огороженный Сад</string>
		<string lang="es">El Jardín Hermético</string>
		<string lang="kr">벽 안의 정원</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">O Jardim Murado</string>
</set>
<set id="name-act-1">
		<string lang="de">Quer durch die$br$sichere Zone</string>
		<string lang="en">Across the$br$Perimeter</string>
		<string lang="fr">En Traversant$br$le Perimètre</string>
		<string lang="zh">穿越$br$边界</string>
		<string lang="jp">周辺を越えて</string>
		<string lang="ru">Через Периметр</string>
		<string lang="es">Atravesando el$br$Perímetro</string>
		<string lang="kr">경계를 넘어</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Atravessando o$br$Perímetro</string>
</set>
<set id="name-act-2">
		<string lang="de">Der Ummauerte Garten</string>
		<string lang="en">The Walled Garden</string>
		<string lang="fr">Le Jardin Enclos</string>
		<string lang="zh">围墙内的伊甸园</string>
		<string lang="jp">囲まれた庭</string>
		<string lang="ru">Огороженный Сад</string>
		<string lang="es">El Jardín Amurallado</string>
		<string lang="kr">벽 안의 정원</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">O Jardim Murado</string>
</set>
<set id="prologue-1">
		<string lang="de">Es ist das Jahr 3000 und nochwas.</string>
		<string lang="en">The year is 3000 and something.</string>
		<string lang="fr">L'année est 3000 et quelque chose.</string>
		<string lang="zh">公元3000左右。</string>
		<string lang="jp">西暦3000年とか。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Год 3000 или что-то вроде того.</string>
		<string lang="es">Es el año 3000 y algo.</string>
		<string lang="kr">3000 몇 년 가량의 일입니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">O ano é 3000 e alguma coisa.</string>
</set>
<set id="prologue-2">
		<string lang="de">Die Welt ....</string>
		<string lang="en">The world ...</string>
		<string lang="fr">Le monde ...</string>
		<string lang="zh">整个世界……</string>
		<string lang="jp">この世界……</string>
		<string lang="ru">Мир ....</string>
		<string lang="es">El mundo ...</string>
		<string lang="kr">세계는...</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">O mundo ...</string>
</set>
<set id="prologue-2b">
		<string lang="de">nunja ....</string>
		<string lang="en">well ...</string>
		<string lang="fr">bon ...</string>
		<string lang="zh">砰</string>
		<string lang="jp">うーん……</string>
		<string lang="ru">ну ...</string>
		<string lang="es">bueno ...</string>
		<string lang="kr">음...</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">bem ...</string>
</set>
<set id="prologue-3">
		<string lang="de">sie wurde leider$br$ziemlich zerstört.</string>
		<string lang="en">let's say it's gotten$br$pretty much destroyed.</string>
		<string lang="fr">elle malheureusement a été détruite.</string>
		<string lang="zh">可以说是$br$几乎变成了一片废墟。</string>
		<string lang="jp">それは基本的に破壊$br$されたとしましょう。</string>
		<string lang="ru">давайте скажем, что он был$br$типа разрушен.</string>
		<string lang="es">digamos que ha quedado$br$bastante destrozado.</string>
		<string lang="kr">세계가 꽤$br$파괴된 상태라고 가정해보죠.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">digamos que foi$br$bastante destruído.</string>
</set>
<set id="prologue-4">
		<string lang="de">Die wenigen Überlebenden der $b$Gravistrophe$/b$ leben in verstreuten Wohnlagern von gravitonischen Energiespitzen.</string>
		<string lang="en">The few survivors of the $b$Gravistrophe$/b$$br$live in scattered campsites$br$off gravitonic energy spikes.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Les quelques survivants de la $b$Gravistrophe$/b$$br$vivent dans des campements éparpillés$br$de crêtes d'énergie gravitonique.</string>
		<string lang="zh">$b$引力扭转$/b$后的少数幸存者$br$纷纷避开引力高峰区$br$四处安营扎寨。</string>
		<string lang="jp">$b$重力の大惨事$/b$ の後、$br$いくつかの生存者は、重力エネルギーのスパイクから小さなキャンプに住んでいます。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Несколько выживших из $b$Гравистрофы$/b$$br$живут в разбросанных лагерях, укрываясь$br$от гравитонных энергетических шипов.</string>
		<string lang="es">Los pocos supervivientes de la $b$gravístrofe$/b$$br$viven en campamentos dispersados$br$sobre picos de energía gravitónica.</string>
		<string lang="kr">$b$중력 재앙$/b$에서 살아남은 소수의 생존자들은$br$중력 에너지 폭주와 멀찍이 떨어진 야영지에$br$뿔뿔이 흩어져 살고 있습니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Os poucos sobreviventes da $b$gravístrofe$/b$$br$vivem em acampamentos dispersos$br$de picos de energia gravitônica.</string>
</set>
</localization>