<localization>
<set id="name-chapter-bogmarshes">
		<string lang="de">Moorsümpfe</string>
		<string lang="en">Bogmarshes</string>
		<string lang="fr">Marais palustre</string>
		<string lang="zh">沼泽</string>
		<string lang="jp">沼地</string>
		<string lang="ru">Болотные топи</string>
		<string lang="es">Pantanos</string>
		<string lang="kr">습지</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Pântanos</string>
</set>
<set id="name-chapter-dinosaurgraveyard">
		<string lang="de">Dynosaurier-Friedhof</string>
		<string lang="en">Dynosaur Graveyard</string>
		<string lang="fr">Cimetière de Dynosaures</string>
		<string lang="zh">恐龙墓地</string>
		<string lang="jp">ダイナソー墓地</string>
		<string lang="ru">Кладбище динозавров</string>
		<string lang="es">Cementerio de Dinosaurios</string>
		<string lang="kr">공룡 묘지</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Cemitério de Dinossauros</string>
</set>
<set id="name-chapter-eden">
		<string lang="de">Eden</string>
		<string lang="en">Eden</string>
		<string lang="fr">Eden</string>
		<string lang="zh">伊甸园</string>
		<string lang="jp">エデン</string>
		<string lang="ru">Эдем</string>
		<string lang="es">Edén</string>
		<string lang="kr">에덴</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Éden</string>
</set>
<set id="name-chapter-lavacaves">
		<string lang="de">Vulkan</string>
		<string lang="en">Volcano</string>
		<string lang="fr">Volcan</string>
		<string lang="zh">火山</string>
		<string lang="jp">火山</string>
		<string lang="ru">Вулкан</string>
		<string lang="es">Volcán</string>
		<string lang="kr">화산</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Vulcão</string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-bogmarshes">
		<string lang="de">Normalerweise zersetzen sich Moore langsam, aber durch das instabile Grav.-Feld hier vergeht die Zeit stoßweise.$br$Torf wird an einem Nachmittag zu Kohle. Die Mangroven wachsen so schnell, dass man sie quietschen hört. Bleibt von den Pilzsporen fern, sonst verpasst ihr das Abendessen!$br$Außerdem – holt euch keine nassen Socken.</string>
		<string lang="en">Bogs are supposed to decompose slowly, but with the unstable grav. field here, time moves in fits and starts.$br$Peat turns into coal in an afternoon. The mangroves grow so quick you can hear ‘em squeak. Don’t get near the mushroom spores, or you’ll blink and miss dinner!$br$Also, try to keep your socks dry.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Les marais sont censés se décomposer lentement, mais avec le champ grav. instable ici, le temps passe en saccades.$br$L'après-midi, le tourbe se transforme en charbon. Les mangroves poussent si vite que vous pouvez les entendre gémir. Ne vous approchez pas des spores de champignons, sinon vous manquerez le dîner!$br$</string>
		<string lang="zh">沼泽通常是缓慢腐败的，但在不稳定的引力场中，时间可能会断断续续。$br$泥炭在一个下午内变成煤。红树林高速生长，吱吱作响。不要靠近蘑菇孢子，否则你可能会在一眨眼间错过下一顿晚餐$br$</string>
		<string lang="jp">沼地は通常はゆっくりと分解されるはずですが、ここに不安定な重力場があるため、時間は一瞬一瞬になります。$br$石炭は午後になると石炭になります。マングローブはとても速く育ち、ゴーグルをかけているときに聞こえる音がします。キノコの孢子に近づかないでください、そうしないと夕食を食べるのを見逃してしまいます$br$</string>
		<string lang="ru">Болота должны разлагаться медленно, но с нестабильным грав. полем здесь, время движется рывками.$br$Торф превращается в уголь за один вечер. Мангровые деревья растут так быстро, что вы можете услышать их писк. Не подходите к спорам грибов, иначе вы моргнете и пропустите ужин!$br$Так же попытайтесь держать свои носки сухими</string>
		<string lang="es">Los pantanos se supone que se descomponen lentamente, pero con el campo grav. inestable aquí, el tiempo se mueve a tirones.$br$La turba se convierte en carbón en una tarde. Los manglares crecen tan rápido que puedes oírlos chirriar. No te acerques a las esporas de los hongos !O parpadearás y te perderás la cena!$br$</string>
		<string lang="kr">습지는 습기가 많습니다. 습지는 습기가 많습니다. 습지는 습기가 가장 많습니다.$br$우리는 거대한 두꺼비와 지성을 가진 버섯을 볼 수 있습니다. 누군가가 뒤에 모듈을 놓아 두었는지 눈을 뜨고 있으십시오. $br$</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Pântanos são supostos se decompor lentamente, mas com o campo grav. instável aqui, o tempo se move em solavancos.$br$Turfa se transforma em carvão em uma tarde. Os manguezais crescem tão rápido que você pode ouvi-los chiar. Não se aproxime das esporas dos cogumelos, ou você piscará e perderá o jantar!$br$</string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-dinosaurgraveyard">
		<string lang="de"></string>
		<string lang="en">In these wastelands, a powerful Grav. Blast must have unextincted the dinosaurs. And then re-extincted them. And then re-unextincted them.$p$This is the only explanation I can come up with for why they are at the same time fossilized and roaming the earth.$p$Yikes. Those footprints look big!</string>
		<string lang="fr"></string>
		<string lang="zh"></string>
		<string lang="jp"></string>
		<string lang="ru"></string>
		<string lang="es"></string>
		<string lang="kr"></string>
		<string lang="pt-br"></string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-eden">
		<string lang="de">Als der Verschlossene Garten angekündigt wurde, brach unter den Mächtigen ein heftiger Kampf aus. Niemand ergatterte einen Platz, ohne Blut an den Händen zu haben.$br$Jede Minute hinter dem Zeitdamm trocknet Jahrzehnte aus dem Leben unterhalb. Eine unheimliche Stille legt sich über die Stadt – als wäre alles eingefroren.$br$Nach Tausenden von Jahren gibt es nichts mehr zu sagen.</string>
		<string lang="en">When the Walled Garden was announced, a most violent struggle erupted among the powerful. No one got to live here without blood on their hands.$br$Every minute behind the time dam dries up decades from all life below. An eerie silence blankets the city – as though everything was frozen.$br$After thousands of years, there’s nothing left to say.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Lorsque le Jardin Clos fut annoncé, une lutte violente éclata parmi les puissants. Personne ne put y vivre sans avoir du sang sur les mains.$br$Chaque minute derrière le barrage temporel assèche des décennies de vie en dessous. Un silence étrange recouvre la ville – comme si tout était gelé.$br$Après des milliers d'années, il n'y a plus rien à dire.</string>
		<string lang="zh">当封闭花园被宣布时，强大者之间爆发了激烈的斗争。没有人能在这里生活而不带着鲜血。$br$时间堤后的每一分钟都会从下面的生命中抽干数十年。一种怪异的寂静笼罩着这座城市——仿佛一切都被冻结了。$br$数千年后，没有什么可说的了。</string>
		<string lang="jp">封鎖された庭園が発表されたとき、強者の間で激しい争いが勃発しました。誰もが手に血をつけずにここで生きることはできませんでした。$br$時間のダムの後ろの一分一秒が、下のすべての生命から数十年を乾燥させます。不気味な静けさがこの街を覆い、まるですべてが凍結しているかのようです。$br$数千年後、言うことは何もありません。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Когда был объявлен Запертый Сад, между могущественными разразилась жестокая борьба. Никто не мог здесь жить, не имея крови на руках.$br$Каждая минута за временной плотиной высушивает десятилетия жизни внизу. Жуткое молчание покрывает город – как будто всё замерло.$br$После тысячелетий, больше нечего сказать.</string>
		<string lang="es">Cuando se anunció el Jardín Hermético, estalló una lucha violenta entre los poderosos. Nadie consiguió vivir aquí sin sangre en sus manos.$br$Cada minuto detrás de la presa del tiempo seca décadas de vida de abajo. Un silencio inquietante cubre la ciudad, como si todo estuviera congelado.$br$Después de miles de años, no queda nada que decir.</string>
		<string lang="kr">봉쇄된 정원이 발표되자 강력한 사람들 사이에 격렬한 싸움이 벌어졌습니다. 아무도 손에 피를 흘리지 않고 여기에서 살 수 없었습니다.$br$시간 댐 뒤의 매분마다 아래의 모든 생명에서 수십 년을 건조합니다. 기이한 침묵이 도시를 덮습니다. 마치 모든 것이 얼어붙은 것처럼요.$br$수천 년 후에는 더 이상 할 말이 없습니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Quando o Jardim Fechado foi anunciado, uma luta violenta irrompeu entre os poderosos. Ninguém conseguiu viver aqui sem sangue em suas mãos.$br$Cada minuto atrás da barragem do tempo seca décadas de vida de baixo. Um silêncio inquietante cobre a cidade, como se tudo estivesse congelado.$br$Depois de milhares de anos, não há mais nada a dizer.</string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-lavacaves">
		<string lang="de">Das Krabbeln in der Dunkelheit ist eine weitere seltsame Sammlung von Kreaturen. Sie haben hier unten für komprimierte Eonen gelebt und können den Eruptionen leicht ausweichen.$br$Wir müssen aufpassen wohin und vor allem wann wir treten, um die Lavastöße zu vermeiden.$br$Wir sollten wahrscheinlich unsere Mäntel ausziehen.</string>
		<string lang="en">That skittering in the dark is another strange collection of creatures. They have lived down here for compressed eons and can easily avoid the eruptions.$br$We will have to watch where and when we step in order to avoid the emissions of lava.$br$We should probably take off our coats.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Ces ondulations dans la pénombre sont la manifestation d'étranges créatures. Elles vivent ici bas pour des eons compressés et peuvent aisément éviter les éruptions.$br$Nous devrons être vigilant à où et quand nous devrons poser nos pieds, afin d'éviter les éruptions volcaniques.$br$Nous devrions enelever nos vestes.</string>
		<string lang="zh">黑暗中的爬行是另一种奇怪的生物。它们在这里生活了数百万年，可以轻松地避开喷发。$br$我们必须小心地观察我们的脚步，以避免熔岩的喷发。$br$我们可能应该脱掉我们的外套。</string>
		<string lang="jp">暗闇の中での這い回る音は、別の奇妙な生物の集まりです。彼らは圧縮されたエオンの間ここで生活しており、噴火を簡単に避けることができます。$br$我々はどこに、そしていつ踏むべきかを見極めるために注意を払わなければなりません。$br$私たちはおそらくコートを脱ぐべきです。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Это ползание в темноте – ещё одна странная коллекция существ. Они живут здесь в течение сжатых эонов и могут легко избегать извержений.$br$Нам придётся следить за тем, куда и когда мы ступаем, чтобы избежать выбросов лавы.$br$Мы, вероятно, должны снять свои пальто.</string>
		<string lang="es">Ese corretear en la oscuridad es otra extraña colección de criaturas. Han vivido aquí abajo por eones comprimidos y pueden eludir fácilmente las erupciones.$br$Debemos vigilar dónde y cuándo pisamos para evitar las emisiones de lava.$br$Probablemente deberíamos quitarnos los abrigos.</string>
		<string lang="kr">어둠 속에서 기어다니는 것은 또 다른 이상한 생물들의 집합입니다. 그들은 여기에서 압축된 시대 동안 살았으며, 용암 분출을 쉽게 피할 수 있습니다.$br$우리는 용암의 분출을 피하기 위해 어디에 언제 발을 디뎌야 하는지 주의를 기울여야 합니다.$br$아마 우리는 외투를 벗어야 할 것입니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Aquele rastejar na escuridão é outra estranha coleção de criaturas. Elas viveram aqui por éons comprimidos e podem facilmente evitar as erupções.$br$Precisaremos observar onde e quando pisamos para evitar as emissões de lava.$br$Provavelmente deveríamos tirar nossos casacos.</string>
</set>
</localization>