<localization>
<set id="act">
		<string lang="de">Teil</string>
		<string lang="en">Part</string>
		<string lang="fr">Part</string>
		<string lang="zh">部分</string>
		<string lang="jp">幕</string>
		<string lang="ru">Часть</string>
		<string lang="es">Parte</string>
		<string lang="kr">파트</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Parte</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">部分
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Частина</string>
</set>
<set id="act-1">
		<string lang="de">Teil I:</string>
		<string lang="en">Part I:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Part I:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第一部分</string>
		<string lang="jp">第1幕</string>
		<string lang="ru">Часть I:</string>
		<string lang="es">Parte I:</string>
		<string lang="kr">파트 I:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Parte I:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">第一部分
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Частина I:</string>
</set>
<set id="act-2">
		<string lang="de">Teil II:</string>
		<string lang="en">Part II:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Part II:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第二部分</string>
		<string lang="jp">第2幕</string>
		<string lang="ru">Часть II:</string>
        <string lang="es">Parte II:</string>
		<string lang="kr">파트 II:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Parte II:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">第二部分</string>
		<string lang="uk">Частина II:</string>
</set>
<set id="act-3">
		<string lang="de">Teil III:</string>
		<string lang="en">Part III:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Part III:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第三部分</string>
		<string lang="jp">第3幕</string>
		<string lang="kr">파트 III:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">第三部分
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Частина III:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle1-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel I:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter I:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre I:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第一章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">第1章</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава I:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo I:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 I:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo I:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">第一章：
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Розділ I:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle1-story">
		<string lang="de">Es ist Getreidefest.$br$Nana Slopper war gerade dabei, einen gravioaktiven Truthahn in den Ofen zu schieben, als der Plasmazähler auf Null fiel.$br$Jemand sollte losziehen und erforschen, was den Ärger dieses Mal verursachte.</string>
		<string lang="en">It's grain festival.$br$Nana Slopper was about to put a gravioactive turkey in the oven when the plasma meter hit zero.$br$Someone should go and investigate what caused the ruckus this time.</string>
		<string lang="fr">C'est fête des céréales.$br$Mamie Slopper était sur le point de mettre une dinde gravioactive dans le four lorsque le compteur à plasma indique zéro.$br$Quelqu'un devrait aller $b$chercher du plasma$/b$ et étudier ce qui a causé la panne de ce fois-ci.</string>
		<string lang="zh">今天是谷物节。$br$斯洛普奶奶正要将引力火鸡塞进烤箱中，却发现等离子仪归零了。$br$该派人去查一查到底怎么回事。</string>
		<string lang="jp">今日は収穫祭。$br$ナナ・スロッパーが重力育ちの七面鳥をオーブンに入れようとしたら、プラズマ・メーターがゼロになった。$br$誰かがこの騒動の原因を調査しないと</string>
		<string lang="ru">Это фестиваль зерна.$br$Нана Слоппер собиралась положить гравиоактивную индейку в духовку, когда плазменный счетчик упал до нуля.$br$Кто-то должен пойти и выяснить, что вызвало проблемы на этот раз.</string>
		<string lang="es">Es el festival del grano.$br$Nana Slopper estaba a punto de poner un pavo gravioactivo en el horno cuando el medidor de plasma llegó a cero.$br$Alguien debería ir e investigar qué causó el alboroto esta vez.</string>
		<string lang="kr">곡물 잔치 기간입니다.$br$나나 슬로퍼가 중력 활성 칠면조를 오븐에 넣으려고 하기 직전에, 플라즈마 미터가 0을 기록했습니다.$br$이번 소동이 발생한 원인을 누군가 가서 조사해야만 합니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">É o festival do grão.$br$Nana Slopper estava prestes a colocar um peru gravioativo no forno quando o medidor de plasma atingiu zero.$br$Alguém deveria ir e investigar o que causou a confusão desta vez.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">今天是穀物節。$br$斯洛普奶奶正要將引力火雞塞進烤箱中，卻發現等離子儀歸零了。$br$該派人去查一查到底怎麼回事。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Свято зерна.$br$Бабця Слоппер збиралася поставити гравіоактивну індичку в духовку, коли лічильник плазми став на нуль.$br$Комусь слід піти і розібратись, що сталося цього разу.</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle1-title">
		<string lang="de">Blackout</string>
		<string lang="en">Blackout</string>
		<string lang="fr">Blackout</string>
		<string lang="zh">断电</string>
		<string lang="jp">停電</string>
		<string lang="ru">Блэкаут</string>
		<string lang="es">Apagón</string>
		<string lang="kr">암전</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Apagão</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">斷電
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Затемнення</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle2-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel II:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter II:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre II:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第二章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">第2章</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава II:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo II:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 II:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo II:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">第二章：
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Розділ II:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle2-story">
		<string lang="de">$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“Der Gyrograph ist völlig am durchdrehen. Und schaut euch mein Frühstück an! Das Rührei hat sich entrührt!$br$Wenn wir nicht verstehen, was die Zeitverzerrungen verursacht, riskieren wir, selbst … entrührt … zu werden.”</string>
		<string lang="en">$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“The gyrograph is all over the place. And look at my breakfast! These eggs have unscrambled themselves!$br$If we don’t understand what’s causing the time distortions we risk getting … unscrambled … too.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“Le gyrographe est complètement détraqué. Et regardez mon petit-déjeuner! Les œufs se sont déscramblés!$br$Si nous ne comprenons pas ce qui cause les distorsions temporelles, nous risquons de nous faire … déscrambler … aussi.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“到处都是漩涡。看看我的早餐！这些鸡蛋全都乱码了！$br$如果不尽快搞清楚造成时间扭曲的原因，我们很有可能……也会……变成乱码。”</string>
		<string lang="jp">$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$「時空計が乱れてる。しかも、見てよアタシの朝飯！$br$スクランブル・エッグが卵に戻っちゃってる！$br$時間の歪みの原因がわかんないとアタシらだって……$br$卵に戻るかも……」</string>
		<string lang="ru">$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“Гирограф полностью вышел из строя. И посмотрите на мой завтрак — эти яйца взбились сами! Если мы не выясним, что вызывает временные искажения, рискуем сами... так же... взбиться.”</string>
		<string lang="es">$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“El giroscopio está completamente descontrolado. ¡Y mira mi desayuno! ¡Estos huevos se han desrevuelto ellos solos!$br$Si no entendemos qué está causando las distorsiones temporales, corremos el riesgo de … desrevolvernos … también.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“자이로그래프가 사방에 널려있어요. 그리고 제 아침 좀 봐요! 계란들이 멋대로 원래대로 돌아가고 있잖아요!$br$시간 왜곡의 원인을 정확히 파악하지 못하면 어쩌면 우리도...원래대로...돌아가버릴 거에요.“</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“O giroscópio está completamente descontrolado. E olha meu café da manhã! Esses ovos se desembaralharam sozinhos!$br$Se não entendermos o que está causando as distorções temporais, corremos o risco de … nos desembaralharmos … também.”</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“到處都是漩渦。看看我的早餐！這些雞蛋全都亂碼了！$br$如果不盡快搞清楚造成時間扭曲的原因，我們很有可能……也會……變成亂碼。”
</string>
		<string lang="uk">$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$«Гірограф повністю вийшов з ладу. І тільки поглянь на мій сніданок! Ця яєшня розʼяєшнилась!$br$Якщо не розуміємо причину спотворення часу, нас може теж… розʼяєшнити…»</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle2-title">
		<string lang="de">Verdrehte Logik</string>
		<string lang="en">Scrambled Logic</string>
		<string lang="fr">Logique Tordue</string>
		<string lang="zh">时空干扰</string>
		<string lang="jp">スクランブル・ロジック</string>
		<string lang="ru">Логика дала сбой</string>
		<string lang="es">Lógica Revuelta</string>
		<string lang="kr">뒤죽박죽 논리</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Lógica Embaralhada</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">時空干擾
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Заплутана логіка</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle3-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel III:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter III:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre III:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第三章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">第3章</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава III:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo III:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 III:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo III:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">第三章：
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Розділ III:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle3-story">
		<string lang="de">$playercharacter-alice-icon$“Die ersten Jahre der Gravitonikforschung waren schrecklich ereignislos. Wir verbrachten Jahre damit, zu berechnen, wie sich das menschliche Leben mittels Zeitdilatation verlängern lässt.$br$Die Theorie war solide, aber es bestand die Gefahr eines katastrophalen Zeitlecks.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Was ist dann passiert?”$p$$playercharacter-alice-icon$“Das Projekt wurde plötzlich eingestellt und alle wurden rausgeschmissen”</string>
		<string lang="en">$playercharacter-alice-icon$“The first years of gravitonics research were terribly uneventful. We spent years calculating the potential of time dilation to prolong human life. The theory was sound, but there was a risk of catastrophic time spillage onto the environment.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“What happened then?”$p$$playercharacter-alice-icon$“The project went dark and everybody got kicked off.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">$playercharacter-alice-icon$“Les premières années de la recherche en gravitonique étaient terriblement ennuyeuses. Nous avons passé des années à calculer le potentiel de la dilatation du temps pour prolonger la vie humaine.$br$La théorie était solide, mais il y avait un risque de déversement temporel catastrophique dans l'environnement.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Qu'est-il arrivé ensuite?”$p$$playercharacter-alice-icon$“Le projet a été arrêté brusquement et tout le monde a été viré.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">$playercharacter-alice-icon$“引力研究之初一切风平浪静。我们花了数年时间计算通过时间膨胀来延长人类寿命的可能性。理论上是可行的，但伴随的风险，时间溢出对环境的影响，也是灾难性的。”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“后来呢？”$p$$playercharacter-alice-icon$“项目中断，所有人被踢了出来。”</string>
		<string lang="jp">$playercharacter-alice-icon$「重力科学研究の黎明期は、ずいぶんのんびりだったね。人間の寿命を延ばせないか、時間拡張の可能性を算出するのに何年もかけてたよ。理論的には正しかったけど、環境に壊滅的な時間漏出をもたらす恐れが見つかっちゃって」$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$「で、どうなったの？」$p$$playercharacter-alice-icon$「プロジェクトは暗礁に乗り上げ、みんな追い出されちゃった」</string>
		<string lang="ru">$playercharacter-alice-icon$“Первые годы исследований гравитоники были ужасно скучными. Мы потратили годы на расчет потенциала временного растяжения для продления человеческой жизни. Теория была почти железобетонной, но существовала опасность катастрофического временного разлива в окружающую среду.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Что случилось потом?”$p$$playercharacter-alice-icon$“Проект внезапно закрылся, и всех выгнали.”</string>
		<string lang="es">$playercharacter-alice-icon$“Los primeros años de la investigación gravitonica fueron terriblemente aburridos. Pasamos años calculando el potencial de la dilatación del tiempo para prolongar la vida humana. La teoría era sólida, pero existía el riesgo de un derrame temporal catastrófico en el medio ambiente.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“¿Qué pasó entonces?”$p$$playercharacter-alice-icon$“El proyecto se detuvo de repente y todos fueron despedidos.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">$playercharacter-alice-icon$“처음 중력학 연구를 시작한 해에는 딱히 별다른 일이 없었어. 인간의 생명을 연장시킬 시간 팽창의 가능성을 계산하는 데에 몇 년을 소비했지. 이론은 논리적으로 타당했지만, 주변에 대규모 시간 유출이 발생할 위험성이 있었어.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“그리고 무슨 일이 일어났죠?”$p$$playercharacter-alice-icon$“프로젝트는 중단됐고 모든 사람들이 쫓겨났지.”</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">$playercharacter-alice-icon$“Os primeiros anos de pesquisa gravitônica foram terrivelmente monótonos. Passamos anos calculando o potencial da dilatação do tempo para prolongar a vida humana. A teoria era sólida, mas havia o risco de um derramamento temporal catastrófico no ambiente.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“O que aconteceu então?”$p$$playercharacter-alice-icon$“O projeto foi interrompido de repente e todos foram demitidos.”</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">$playercharacter-alice-icon$“引力研究之初一切風平浪靜。我們花了數年時間計算通過時間膨脹來延長人類壽命的可能性。理論上是可行的，但伴隨的風險，時間溢出對環境的影響，也是災難性的。”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“後來呢？”$p$$playercharacter-alice-icon$“專案中斷，所有人被踢了出來。”
</string>
		<string lang="uk">$playercharacter-alice-icon$«Перші роки досліджень гравітоніки пройшли жахливо нудно. Ми витратили роки на розрахунок потенціалу затримки часу для продовження людського життя. Теорія була обґрунтованою, але існував ризик катастрофічного виливу часу у навколишнє середовище.»$p$ $playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$«Що було далі?»$p$ $playercharacter-alice-icon$«Проєкт раптово зупинився, і всіх розігнали.»</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle3-title">
		<string lang="de">Ebbe und Flut</string>
		<string lang="en">Ebb and Flow</string>
		<string lang="fr">Basse et Haute</string>
		<string lang="zh">潮起潮落</string>
		<string lang="jp">山あり谷あり</string>
		<string lang="ru">Прилив и отлив</string>
		<string lang="es">Flujo y Reflujo</string>
		<string lang="kr">밀물과 썰물</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Fluxo e Refluxo</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">潮起潮落
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Прилив та відлив</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle4-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel IV:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter IV:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre IV:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第四章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">第4章</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава IV:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo IV:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 IV:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo IV:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">第四章：
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Розділ IV:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle4-story">
		<string lang="de">$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“Wenn ihr diese Nachricht hört, bedeutet es, dass etwas furchtbar schief gelaufen ist.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Es ist Opa Sloppers Stimme!”$p$$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“Sie bauen eine schwebende Stadt, und sie umschließen sie mit einem Damm, der den Fluss der Zeit stoppt. Sie tauften sie Eden. Sie waren nicht sehr kreativ.”</string>
		<string lang="en">$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“If you're hearing this message, it means that things have gone terribly wrong.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“It’s Grandpa Slopper’s voice!”$p$$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“They’re building a floating city, around which they're constructing a dam to halt the flow of time. They called it Eden. They weren’t very creative.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“Si vous entendez ce message, cela signifie que les choses ont terriblement mal tourné.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“C'est la voix de Papi Slopper!”$p$$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“Ils construisent une ville flottante, autour de laquelle ils construisent un barrage pour arrêter le flux du temps. Ils l'ont appelée Eden.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“如果你收到这条消息，就意味着形势已经相当危急了。”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“是斯洛普爷爷的声音！”$p$$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“它们正在建造一座浮空的城市，并在其周围修建了一圈大坝来阻止时间的流动。他们称之为伊甸园。很没有新意的名字。”</string>
		<string lang="jp">$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$「このメッセージを聞いとるなら、事態は深刻な状況下にあるということよの」$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$「爺ちゃんの声だ！」$p$$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$「連中は浮遊都市を建設しとる。時間の流れをせき止めるダムを周囲に建造しながらの。その名もエデン。独自性には欠けとるな。儂は、重力科学の最終公理を隠さにゃならん。一番、関与しそうにない者にの」</string>
		<string lang="ru">$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“Если вы слышите это сообщение, это означает, что что-то пошло ужасно не так.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Это голос дедушки Слоппера!”$p$$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“Они строят плавающий город с окружающей его плотиной, чтобы остановить поток времени. Они назвали его Эден. Они не были особо креативны.”</string>
		<string lang="es">$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“Si estás escuchando este mensaje, significa que las cosas han salido terriblemente mal.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“¡Es la voz del abuelo Slopper!”$p$$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“Están construyendo una ciudad flotante, alrededor de la cual están construyendo un dique para detener el flujo del tiempo. La llamaron Edén. No fueron muy creativos.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“만약 이 메시지를 듣고 있다면, 상황이 굉장히 좋지 않게 돌아가고 있다는 뜻이겠구만.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“슬로퍼 할아버지 목소리야!”$p$$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“그 자들이 공중 도시를 건설하고, 시간의 흐름을 막기 위해 댐을 만들었어. 에덴이라고 부르더군. 창의력하고는.”</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“Se você está ouvindo esta mensagem, significa que as coisas deram terrivelmente errado.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“É a voz do vovô Slopper!”$p$$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“Eles estão construindo uma cidade flutuante, em torno da qual estão construindo uma barragem para interromper o fluxo do tempo. Eles a chamaram de Éden. Eles não foram muito criativos.”</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“如果你收到這條消息，就意味著形勢已經相當危急了。”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“是斯洛普爺爺的聲音！”$p$$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$“它們正在建造一座浮空的城市，並在其周圍修建了一圈大壩來阻止時間的流動。他們稱之為伊甸園。很沒有新意的名字。”</string>
		<string lang="uk">$playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$«Якщо ви чуєте це повідомлення, це означає, що все пішло не так.»$p$ $playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$«Це голос Дідуся Слоппера!»$p$ $playercharacter-plasmamech-icon$«Вони будують плавуче місто, навколо якого будують дамбу, що має зупинити плин часу. Вони назвали це Едемом. Не надто оригінально.»</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle4-title">
		<string lang="de">Eine Stadt in den Wolken</string>
		<string lang="en">A City in the Skies</string>
		<string lang="fr">Une Ville dans les Cieux</string>
		<string lang="zh">浮空之城</string>
		<string lang="jp">浮遊都市</string>
		<string lang="ru">Город в небесах</string>
		<string lang="es">Una Ciudad en los Cielos</string>
		<string lang="kr">하늘 위의 도시</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Uma Cidade nos Céus</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">浮空之城</string>
		<string lang="uk">Місто в небі</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle5-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel V:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter V:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre V:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第五章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">第5章</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава V:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo V:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 V:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo V:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">第五章：
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Розділ V:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle5-story">
		<string lang="de">$playercharacter-ninja-icon$“Lange Zeit gab es Gerüchte von Leuten, die unsere Zeit stehlen. Niemand hat damals zugehört, und jetzt schau dir alles an! Du hast sicher auch Leute verloren. Ich kann nicht ruhen, bis ich die Verantwortlichen gefunden habe.”</string>
		<string lang="en">$playercharacter-ninja-icon$“For the longest time there have been rumours of people stealing our time. Nobody listened back then, and now look at everything! You must have lost people too. I can't rest until I've found those responsible.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">$playercharacter-ninja-icon$“Pendant longtemps, il y a eu des rumeurs de gens volant notre temps. Personne n'écoutait à l'époque, et maintenant regardez tout! Vous avez sûrement aussi perdu des gens. Je ne peux pas me reposer tant que je n'ai pas trouvé les responsables.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">“抱歉打扰了你的全息直播，杰西，但我们有理由相信拯救世界的关键，就藏在你脑海中的某处。”$br$– “呃……并没有。”$br$“杰西！想想爷爷最后跟你说了什么？”$br$– “我不确……什么玫瑰和紫罗兰，还有时间质量和引力能量的平方成反比什么的。”</string>
		<string lang="jp">「ホロ通信の邪魔して悪い、ジェシー。でも世界を救う鍵は、お前のオツムに残されてるはずなんだ」$br$「いや……別に」$br$「ジェス！爺ちゃんの最後の言葉、覚えてない？」$br$「全然……バラとスミレがどうとかさ、時間質量は重力エネルギーの二乗に反比例するとか……それぐらい」</string>
		<string lang="ru">$playercharacter-ninja-icon$“Долгое время ходили слухи, что люди крадут наше время. Тогда никто не слушал, а теперь посмотрите на все! Вы наверняка тоже потеряли людей. Я не смогу успокоиться, пока не найду виновных.”</string>
		<string lang="es">$playercharacter-ninja-icon$“Durante mucho tiempo hubo rumores de personas que nos robaban el tiempo. Nadie escuchó en aquel entonces, y ahora mira todo esto! Seguro que tú también has perdido gente. No puedo descansar hasta que encuentre a los responsables.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">홀로스트림을 방해해서 미안하지만, 제시, 우린 세상을 구할 열쇠가 너의 머릿속에 있다고 믿는다.""""$br$–""""어...아뇨.""""$br$""""제스! 할아버지가 마지막으로 너한테 남기신 말이 뭐지?""""$br$–""""몰라요...그냥 장미랑 제비꽃에 관한 얘기랑 시간 질량은 중력 에너지 제곱에 반비례한다고 하셨어요."</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">$playercharacter-ninja-icon$“Por muito tempo houve rumores de pessoas roubando nosso tempo. Ninguém ouviu naquela época, e agora olhe tudo isso! Você deve ter perdido pessoas também. Não posso descansar até encontrar os responsáveis.”</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">“抱歉打擾了你的全息直播，傑西，但我們有理由相信拯救世界的關鍵，就藏在你腦海中的某處。”$br$– “呃……並沒有。”$br$“傑西！想想爺爺最後跟你說了什麼？”$br$– “我不確……什麼玫瑰和紫羅蘭，還有時間品質和引力能量的平方成反比什麼的。”
</string>
		<string lang="uk">$playercharacter-ninja-icon$«Довгий час ходили чутки про те, що наш час крадуть. Тоді ніхто не слухав, а тепер дивіться! Ви, мабуть, теж втратили людей. Не заспокоюся, поки не знайду винних.»</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle5-title">
		<string lang="de">Zeitverschwendung</string>
		<string lang="en">A Waste of Time</string>
		<string lang="fr">Perte de Temps</string>
		<string lang="zh">浪费时间</string>
		<string lang="jp">時間の浪費</string>
		<string lang="ru">Потеря времени</string>
		<string lang="es">Pérdida de Tiempo</string>
		<string lang="kr">시간 낭비</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Perda de Tempo</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">浪費時間
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Марна трата часу</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle6-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel VI:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter VI:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre VI:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第六章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">第6章</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава VI:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo VI:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 VI:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo VI:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">第六章：
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Розділ VI:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle6-story">
		<string lang="de">$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“Entschuldigung, dass wir deinen Holo-Stream unterbrechen, Jessy, aber wir glauben, dass der Schlüssel zur Rettung der Welt irgendwo in deinem Kopf gespeichert sein könnte.”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Ähh … nö?”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Jess! Was hat Opa dir als Letztes gesagt, bevor er verschwunden ist?”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Keine Ahnung … irgendwas mit Rosen und Veilchen und dass die zeitliche Masse umgekehrt proportional zur gravitonischen Energie zum Quadrat ist.”</string>
		<string lang="en">$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“Sorry to interrupt your holo-stream, Jessy, but we believe the key to saving the world might be stored somewhere in your mind.”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Yeah … no.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Jess! What’s the last thing Grandpa said to you?”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Dunno … something about roses and violets and the temporal mass being inversely proportional to the gravitonic energy squared.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“Désolé d'interrompre ton holo-streaming, Jessy, mais nous croyons que la clé pour sauver le monde pourrait être stockée quelque part dans ta tête.”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Euh … non.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Jess! Quelle a été la dernière chose que Papi t'a dit?”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Je sais pas … quelque chose à propos de roses et de violettes et que la masse temporelle est inversement proportionnelle à l'énergie gravitonique au carré.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“抱歉打扰了你的全息直播，杰西，但我们有理由相信拯救世界的关键，就藏在你脑海中的某处。”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“呃……并没有。”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“杰西！想想爷爷最后跟你说了什么？”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“我不确……什么玫瑰和紫罗兰，还有时间质量和引力能量的平方成反比什么的。”</string>
		<string lang="jp">$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$「ホロ通信の邪魔して悪い、ジェシー。でも世界を救う鍵は、お前のオツムに残されてるはずなんだ」$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$「いや……別に」$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$「ジェス！爺ちゃんの最後の言葉、覚えてない？」$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$「全然……バラとスミレがどうとかさ、時間質量は重力エネルギーの二乗に反比例するとか……それぐらい」</string>
		<string lang="ru">$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“Извините, что мы прерываем ваш голо-поток, Джесси, но мы считаем, что ключ к спасению мира может быть где-то в вашем разуме.”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Да … нет.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Джесс! Что последнее сказал тебе дедушка?”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Не знаю … что-то о розах и фиалках и о том, что временная масса обратно пропорциональна квадрату гравитонной энергии.”</string>
		<string lang="es">$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“Disculpa interrumpir tu holo-stream, Jessy, pero creemos que la clave para salvar el mundo podría estar almacenada en algún lugar de tu mente.”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Sí … no.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“¡Jess! ¿Qué fue lo último que te dijo el abuelo?”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“No sé … algo sobre rosas y violetas y que la masa temporal es inversamente proporcional al cuadrado de la energía gravitónica.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“홀로스트림을 방해해서 미안하지만, 제시, 우린 세상을 구할 열쇠가 너의 머릿속에 있다고 믿는다.”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“어...아뇨.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“제스! 할아버지가 마지막으로 너한테 남기신 말이 뭐지?”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“몰라요...그냥 장미랑 제비꽃에 관한 얘기랑 시간 질량은 중력 에너지 제곱에 반비례한다고 하셨어요.”</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“Desculpe interromper seu holo-stream, Jessy, mas acreditamos que a chave para salvar o mundo pode estar armazenada em algum lugar de sua mente.”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Sim … não.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Jess! O que foi a última coisa que o vovô disse para você?”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Não sei … algo sobre rosas e violetas e que a massa temporal é inversamente proporcional ao quadrado da energia gravitônica.”</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“抱歉打擾了你的全息直播，傑西，但我們有理由相信拯救世界的關鍵，就藏在你腦海中的某處。”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“呃……並沒有。”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“傑西！想想爺爺最後跟你說了什麼？”$p$$playercharacter-runner-icon$“我不確……什麼玫瑰和紫羅蘭，還有時間品質和引力能量的平方成反比什麼的。”
</string>
		<string lang="uk">$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$«Вибач, що перериваю твою голографічну трансляцію, Джессі, але ми віримо, що ключ до порятунку світу може бути десь у твоїй голові.»$p$ $playercharacter-runner-icon$«Та… ні.»$p$ $playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$«Джес! Що останнє тобі сказав Дідусь?»$p$ $playercharacter-runner-icon$«Не знаю… щось про троянди та фіалки, та те, що темпоральна масу зворотньо пропорційна квадрату гравітонічної енергії.»</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle6-title">
		<string lang="de">Veilchen sind Blau</string>
		<string lang="en">Violets are Blue</string>
		<string lang="fr">Les Violettes sont Bleues</string>
		<string lang="zh">蓝色的紫罗兰</string>
		<string lang="jp">スミレは青し</string>
		<string lang="ru">Фиалки - синие</string>
		<string lang="es">Las Violetas son Azules</string>
		<string lang="kr">제비꽃은 푸르다</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Violetas são Azuis</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">藍色的紫羅蘭
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Фіалки блакитні</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle7-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel VII:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter VII:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre VII:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第七章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">第7章</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава VII:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo VII:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 VII:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo VII:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">第七章：</string>
		<string lang="uk">Розділ VII:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle7-story">
		<string lang="de">$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“Das Wesen einer Falte besteht in einem Knick und einer Verdoppelung.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“Sind wir uns schon einmal begegnet?”$p$$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“Es gibt nicht so etwas wie ‚schon‘. Noch gibt es so etwas wie ‚einmal‘. Wir begegnen uns jetzt. Wir werden uns immer jetzt begegnen. Und ich werde dir immer sagen, dass du dich von diesem Ort fernhalten sollst. Das ist der Knick. Und morgen machst du dich auf den Weg.”</string>
		<string lang="en">$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“The nature of a fold is that of a doubling and a crease.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“Have we met before?”$p$$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“There is no such thing as before. Nor after. We are meeting now. We will always be meeting now. And I will always be telling you to stay away from that place. This is the crease. And tomorrow you will be on your way.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“La nature d'un pli est celle d'un doublement et d'une arête.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“Nous nous sommes déjà rencontrés?”$p$$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“Il n'y a pas de tel chose que ‚déjà‘. Nous nous rencontrons maintenant. Nous nous toujours rencontrerons maintenant. Et je te dirai toujours de rester loin de cet endroit. C'est l'arête. Et demain vous serez en route.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“折叠的本质，是重合加折痕。”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“我们以前见过吗？”$p$$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“不存在所谓的‘以前’。同理没有以后。我们只在此刻相遇。我们永远会在此刻相遇。每一次我都会告诉你不要去那个地方。这就是折痕。而明天你会再次踏上你的征途。”</string>
		<string lang="jp">$playercharacter-nomad-icon$「折り畳みの性質とは、重なりと折り目にある」$p$$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$「誰だっけ？」$p$$playercharacter-nomad-icon$「過去など存在しない。未来もまた存在しない。俺達は、いつだってこんな風に出会い続けている。しかも、その度に俺は、お前へ言い続けているんだ。あの地を離れろ、と。これが折り目だ。そして、お前は明日、旅立つことになる」</string>
		<string lang="ru">$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“Природа складки заключается в удвоении изломе.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“Мы встречались раньше?”$p$$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“Такого понятия, как ‚раньше‘ или ‚позже‘  не существует. Мы встречаемся сейчас. Мы всегда будем встречаться сейчас. И я всегда буду говорить тебе держаться подальше от этого места. Это излом. А завтра ты будешь в пути.”</string>
		<string lang="es">$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“La naturaleza de un pliegue es la de un doblez de una arruga.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“¿Nos hemos conocido antes?”$p$$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“No hay tal cosa como antes. Ni después. Nos estamos conociendo ahora. Siempre nos estaremos conociendo ahora. Y siempre te diré que te mantengas alejado de ese lugar. Esto es la arruga. Y mañana estarás de camino.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“접는 행위의 본질은, 두 배가 되고 주름이 생긴다는 것입니다.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“우리 전에 만난 적 있나요?”$p$$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“전 같은 건 존재하지 않습니다. 이후도 없죠. 우린 지금 만나고 있는 겁니다. 우린 항상 지금 만나게 될 겁니다. 그리고 난 항상 당신에게 그곳에서 멀리 떨어져 있으라고 말하겠죠. 이게 주름이에요. 내일이면 당신은 제 갈 길을 떠날겁니다.”</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“A natureza de uma prega é a de um dobramento e uma ruga.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“Nós já nos conhecemos antes?”$p$$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“Não há tal coisa como antes. Nem depois. Estamos nos conhecendo agora. Estaremos sempre nos conhecendo agora. E eu sempre estarei dizendo para você ficar longe daquele lugar. Esta é a ruga. E amanhã você estará a caminho.”</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“折疊的本質，是重合加折痕。”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$“我們以前見過嗎？”$p$$playercharacter-nomad-icon$“不存在所謂的‘以前’。同理沒有以後。我們只在此刻相遇。我們永遠會在此刻相遇。每一次我都會告訴你不要去那個地方。這就是折痕。而明天你會再次踏上你的征途。”</string>
		<string lang="uk">$playercharacter-nomad-icon$«Природа складки — це подвоєння та згин.»$p$ $playercharacter-slopperjohnson-icon$"Ми раніше не зустрічались?"$p$ $playercharacter-nomad-icon$«Не існує такого поняття, як раніше. Чи пізніше. Ми зустрічаємось зараз. Тепер ми завжди будемо зустрічатися. І я завжди казатиму тобі триматися подалі від цього місця. Це складка. А завтра ти будеш у дорозі.»</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle7-title">
		<string lang="de">Entfaltung</string>
		<string lang="en">Unfolding</string>
		<string lang="fr">Déploiement</string>
		<string lang="zh">展开</string>
		<string lang="jp">折り畳まないで</string>
		<string lang="ru">Разворачивание</string>
		<string lang="es">Despliegue</string>
		<string lang="kr">펼치기</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Desdobramento</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">展開</string>
		<string lang="uk">Розгортання</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle8-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel VIII:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter VIII:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre VIII:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第八章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">第8章</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава VIII:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo VIII:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 VIII:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo VIII:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">第八章：</string>
		<string lang="uk">Розділ VIII:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle8-story">
		<string lang="de">$playercharacter-sol-icon$“Sie wissen genau, welchen Schaden sie anrichten. Aber in ihrer Gier wollen sie in einem unendlichen Tag schwelgen.$br$Der Zeitdamm wird von einer einzigen Energiequelle angetrieben: dem Grav-Reaktor.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Woher weißt du das alles?”$p$$playercharacter-sol-icon$“Weil ich von dort komme.”</string>
		<string lang="en">$playercharacter-sol-icon$“They know exactly about the damage they are causing. But in their greed, they want to revel in an infinite day.$br$ The time dam is powered by a single source of power: the grav reactor.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“How do you know all this?”$p$$playercharacter-sol-icon$“Because I am from there.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">$playercharacter-sol-icon$“Ils savent exactement les dégâts qu'ils causent. Mais dans leur avidité, ils veulent se délecter d'un jour infini.$br$Le barrage temporel est alimenté par une seule source d'énergie: le réacteur gravitationnel.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Comment sais-tu tout ça?”$p$$playercharacter-sol-icon$“Parce que je viens de là-bas.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">$playercharacter-sol-icon$“他们对自己造成的破坏一清二楚。但因为贪婪，他们仍然想纵情享受无限的一天。$br$时间大坝的能量来源只有一个：引力反应堆。”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“你怎么知道的？”$p$$playercharacter-sol-icon$“因为我就来自那里。”</string>
		<string lang="jp">$playercharacter-sol-icon$「奴ら、自分たちが引き起こしてる災害について完全に理解してます。なのに、欲望に負けて、無限の一日を過ごしたがってるんです。時間ダムの動力源はたったひとつ、反重力装置です」$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$「なんで知ってるの？」$p$$playercharacter-sol-icon$「そこから来たものですから」</string>
		<string lang="ru">$playercharacter-sol-icon$“Они точно знают о вреде, который они наносят. Но в своей жадности они хотят наслаждаться бесконечным днем.$br$Временной дам приводится в действие единственным источником энергии: гравитационным реактором.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Откуда ты все это знаешь?”$p$$playercharacter-sol-icon$“Потому что я оттуда.”</string>
		<string lang="es">$playercharacter-sol-icon$“Ellos saben exactamente el daño que están causando. Pero en su codicia, quieren deleitarse en un día infinito.$br$La presa del tiempo es alimentada por una única fuente de energía: el reactor gravitatorio.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“¿Cómo sabes todo esto?”$p$$playercharacter-sol-icon$“Porque soy de allí.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">$playercharacter-sol-icon$“그 자식들은 자기들이 무슨 피해를 끼치고 있는지 정확히 알고 있어. 하지만 탐욕스럽게 무한한 매일을 지내고 싶어하는 거지.$br$시간 댐의 동력원은 딱 하나야: 중력 원자로.”$p$$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“그걸 어떻게 다 알고 계시는 거죠?”$p$$playercharacter-sol-icon$“내가 거기에서 왔거든.”</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">$playercharacter-sol-icon$“Eles sabem exatamente sobre o dano que estão causando. Mas em sua ganância, eles querem se deleitar em um dia infinito.$br$A barragem do tempo é alimentada por uma única fonte de energia: o reator gravitacional.”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“Como você sabe de tudo isso?”$p$$playercharacter-sol-icon$“Porque eu sou de lá.”</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">$playercharacter-sol-icon$“他們對自己造成的破壞一清二楚。但因為貪婪，他們仍然想縱情享受無限的一天。$br$時間大壩的能量來源只有一個：引力反應堆。”$p$$playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$“你怎麼知道的？”$p$$playercharacter-sol-icon$“因為我就來自那裏。”</string>
		<string lang="uk">$playercharacter-sol-icon$«Вони точно знають про шкоду, що завдають. Але у своїй жадобі вони хочуть насолоджуватися нескінченним днем.$br$ Часова дамба живиться від єдиного джерела енергії: гравіреактора.»$p$ $playercharacter-slopperjackson-icon$«Звідки ти все це знаєш?»$p$ $playercharacter-sol-icon$«Бо я звідти.»</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle8-title">
		<string lang="de">Der Ummauerte Garten</string>
		<string lang="en">The Walled Garden</string>
		<string lang="fr">Le Jardin Enclos</string>
		<string lang="zh">围墙内的伊甸园</string>
		<string lang="jp">楽園は檻の中</string>
		<string lang="ru">Огороженный Сад</string>
		<string lang="es">El Jardín Hermético</string>
		<string lang="kr">벽 안의 정원</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">O Jardim Murado</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">圍牆內的伊甸園</string>
		<string lang="uk">Огороджений сад</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle9-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel IX:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter IX:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre IX:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第九章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">第9章</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава IX:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo IX:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 IX:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo IX:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">第九章：</string>
		<string lang="uk">Розділ IX:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle9-story">
        <string lang="de">$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Zuerst dachte ich, die Zeitschleife sei cool, aber es wird langweilig. Die Geschichte zu wiederholen ist bescheuert.”$p$$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“Wir müssen einen Ausweg aus diesem Schlamassel finden. Gibt es eine Möglichkeit, diesen Zeitstrang hinter uns zu lassen?”$p$&lt;size=8&gt;&lt;color=#FFFF80&gt;Schalte den Mech-Hangar im Lager frei.</string> 
		<string lang="en">$playercharacter-runner-icon$“I thought the time loop might be cool but it's getting boring. Repeating history is stupid.”$p$$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“We will have to find a way out of this mess.$br$Is there a way to leave this timeline completely?”$p$&lt;size=8&gt;&lt;color=#FFFF80&gt;Unlock the Mech Hangar in the camp.</string>
        <string lang="fr">$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Je pensais que la boucle temporelle était cool, mais ça devient ennuyeux. Répéter l'histoire est stupide.”$p$$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“Nous devrons trouver un moyen de sortir de ce pétrin. Y a-t-il un moyen de quitter complètement cette ligne temporelle?”$p$&lt;size=8&gt;&lt;color=#FFFF80&gt;Débloquez le hangar de méchas dans le camp.</string>
        <string lang="zh">$playercharacter-runner-icon$“我以为时间循环很酷，但现在有点无聊。重复历史很蠢。”$p$$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“我们必须找到摆脱困境的方法。有没有办法完全离开这个时间线？”$p$&lt;size=8&gt;&lt;color=#FFFF80&gt;在营地解锁机甲库。</string>
        <string lang="jp">$playercharacter-runner-icon$「タイムループは面白いと思ってたけど、もう飽きてきた。歴史を繰り返すのは馬鹿げてる」$p$$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$「この窮地から抜け出す方法を見つけないといけないけど。 この時間軸を完全に離れる方法はあるのかな？」$p$&lt;size=8&gt;&lt;color=#FFFF80&gt;キャンプのメックハンガーを解放してください。</string>
        <string lang="ru">$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Я думал, что временная петля крута, но это становится скучно. Повторять историю глупо.”$p$$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“Нам нужно найти выход из этой передряги. Есть ли сп способ пол ностью покинуть эту временную линию?”$p$&lt;size=8&gt;&lt;color=#FFFF80&gt;Разблокируйте ангар мехов в лагере.</string>
        <string lang="kr">$playercharacter-runner-icon$“시간 루프는 멋있을 줄 알았는데, 이젠 지루해. 역사를 반복하는 건 바보 같아.”$p$$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“우리는 이 난국에서 탈출 방법을 찾아야 하지만. 이 시간선을 완전히 떠날 방법이 있을까요?”$p$&lt;size=8&gt;&lt;color=#FFFF80&gt;캠프의 메카 행거를 해제하세요.</string>
        <string lang="es">$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Pensé que el bucle temporal era genial, pero se está volviendo aburrido. Repetir la historia es estúpido.”$p$$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“Tendremos que encontrar una salida de este lío. ¿Hay alguna manera de dejar completamente esta línea de tiempo?”$p$&lt;size=8&gt;&lt;color=#FFFF80&gt;Desbloquea el hangar de mecas en el campamento.</string>
        <string lang="pt-br">$playercharacter-runner-icon$“Eu achei que o loop temporal era legal, mas está ficando chato. Repetir a história é estúpido.”$p$$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“Teremos que encontrar uma saída desse problema. Existe uma maneira de deixar completamente essa linha do tempo?”$p$&lt;size=8&gt;&lt;color=#FFFF80&gt;Desbloqueie o Hangar de Mechas no acampamento.</string>
        <string lang="zh-tw">$playercharacter-runner-icon$“我以為時間循環很酷，但現在有點無聊。重複歷史很蠢。”$p$$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$“我們必須找到擺脫困境的方法。有沒有辦法完全離開這個時間線？”$p$&lt;size=8&gt;&lt;color=#FFFF80&gt;在營地解鎖機甲庫。</string>
        <string lang="uk">$playercharacter-runner-icon$«Я думав, що часова петля крута, але вже набридло. Повторювати історію — це дурість.»$p$$playercharacter-kimmy-icon$«Нам потрібно знайти вихід з цієї передриги. Чи є спосі б повністю покинути цю часову лінію?»$p$&lt;size=8&gt;&lt;color=#FFFF80&gt;Розблокуйте ангар мехів в таборі.</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle9-title">
		<string lang="de">Tiefer in die Faltung</string>
		<string lang="en">Deeper into the Fold</string>
		<string lang="fr">Plus Profondément dans le Pli</string>
        <string lang="zh">深入折叠</string>
        <string lang="jp">折り畳みの奥へ</string>
        <string lang="ru">Глубже в Складку</string>
        <string lang="es">Más Profundo en el Pliegue</string>
        <string lang="kr">접힌 곳으로</string>
        <string lang="pt-br">Mais Profundo na Dobra</string>
        <string lang="zh-tw">深入折疊</string>
        <string lang="uk">Глибше в Складку</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle10-title">
		<string lang="de">Tiefer in die Faltung</string>
		<string lang="en">Deeper into the Fold</string>
		<string lang="fr">Plus Profondément dans le Pli</string>
        <string lang="zh">深入折叠</string>
        <string lang="jp">折り畳みの奥へ</string>
        <string lang="ru">Глубже в Складку</string>
        <string lang="es">Más Profundo en el Pliegue</string>
        <string lang="kr">접힌 곳으로</string>
        <string lang="pt-br">Mais Profundo na Dobra</string>
        <string lang="zh-tw">深入折疊</string>
        <string lang="uk">Глибше в Складку</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle10-description">
		<string lang="de">Kapitel X:</string>
		<string lang="en">Chapter X:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Chapitre X:</string>
		<string lang="zh">第十章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">第10章</string>
		<string lang="ru">Глава X:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo X:</string>
		<string lang="kr">챕터 X:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo X:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">第十章：</string>
		<string lang="uk">Розділ X:</string>
</set>
<set id="cycle10-story">
		<string lang="de">&lt;color=#78ca9b&gt;Dies ist vorerst das Ende der Geschichte, während wir an neuen Inhalten arbeiten.$p$Teile deine verrücktesten Designs für den Zeitreise-Mech im Discord (Link auf dem Startbildschirm)!$p$$b$Bitte hinterlasse eine Steam-Rezension, das hilft uns am meisten!$/b$$p$Danke, dass du Rogue Voltage spielst.$p$Luca, Entwickler</string>
		<string lang="en">&lt;color=#78ca9b&gt;This is the end of the story for now, while we're developing new content.$p$Share your craziest designs for the Time Travel Mech in the Discord (link on the title screen)!$p$$b$Please leave a Steam review, this helps us a lot!$/b$$p$Thank you for playing Rogue Voltage.$p$Luca, Developer</string>
        <string lang="fr">&lt;color=#78ca9b&gt;C'est la fin de l'histoire pour l'instant, alors que nous travaillons sur de nouveaux contenus.$p$Partagez vos designs les plus fous pour le Mech de Voyage Temporel sur le Discord (lien sur l'écran titre)!$p$S'il vous plaît, laissez une évaluation sur Steam, cela nous aide beaucoup!$p$Merci d'avoir joué à Rogue Voltage.$p$Luca, Développeur</string>
        <string lang="zh">&lt;color=#78ca9b&gt;这暂时是故事的结局。$p$在Discord上分享你对时光机甲的最疯狂设计（链接在标题画面上）！$p$请在Steam上留下评论，这对我们很有帮助！$p$感谢您玩《末日电涌》。$p$Luca，开发者</string>
        <string lang="jp">&lt;color=#78ca9b&gt;これで当面の物語は終わりです。$p$タイムトラベルメックの最もクレイジーなデザインをDiscordで共有してください（タイトル画面にリンクあり）！$p$Steamでレビューを残していただけると助かります！$p$Rogue Voltageをプレイしていただきありがとうございます。$p$Luca、開発者</string>
        <string lang="ru">&lt;color=#78ca9b&gt;Это пока что конец истории.$p$Поделитесь своими самыми безумными дизайнами для меха временных путешествий в Discord (ссылка на главном экране)!$p$Пожалуйста, оставьте отзыв на Steam, это очень поможет нам!$p$Спасибо, что играли в Rogue Voltage.$p$Luca, разработчик</string>
        <string lang="es">&lt;color=#78ca9b&gt;Por ahora, este es el final de la historia.$p$¡Comparte tus diseños más locos para el Mech de Viaje en el Tiempo en Discord (enlace en la pantalla de título)!$p$¡Por favor, deja una reseña en Steam, esto nos ayuda mucho!$p$Gracias por jugar a Rogue Voltage.$p$Luca, Desarrollador</string>
        <string lang="kr">&lt;color=#78ca9b&gt;지금까지의 이야기는 여기까지입니다.$p$디스코드에서 시간 여행 메카를 위한 가장 미친 디자인을 공유하세요(타이틀 화면에 링크)!$p$스팀 리뷰를 남겨주시면 저희에게 큰 도움이 됩니다!$p$로그 볼티지를 플레이해주셔서 감사합니다.$p$Luca, 개발자</string>
        <string lang="pt-br">&lt;color=#78ca9b&gt;Por enquanto, este é o fim da história.$p$Compartilhe seus designs mais loucos para o Mech de Viagem no Tempo no Discord (link na tela de título)!$p$Por favor, deixe uma avaliação no Steam, isso nos ajuda muito!$p$Obrigado por jogar Rogue Voltage.$p$Luca, Desenvolvedor</string>
        <string lang="zh-tw">&lt;color=#78ca9b&gt;這暫時是故事的結局。$p$在Discord上分享你對時光機甲的最瘋狂設計（連結在標題畫面上）！$p$$b$請在Steam上留下評論，這對我們很有幫助！$/b$$p$感謝您玩《末日電湧》。$p$Luca，開發者</string>
        <string lang="uk">&lt;color=#78ca9b&gt;Це поки що кінець історії.$p$Поділіться своїми найбожевільнішими дизайнами для меха часових подорожей в Discord (посилання на головному екрані)!$p$Будь ласка, залиште відгук на Steam, це дуже допоможе нам!$p$Дякуємо, що грали в Rogue Voltage.$p$Luca, розробник</string>
</set>
<set id="cyclefinal-description">
		<string lang="de">Letztes Kapitel:</string>
		<string lang="en">Final Chapter:</string>
		<string lang="fr">Dernier Chapitre:</string>
		<string lang="zh">终章：</string>
		<string lang="jp">最終章</string>
		<string lang="ru">Последняя глава:</string>
		<string lang="es">Capítulo Final:</string>
		<string lang="kr">마지막 챕터:</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Capítulo Final:</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">終章：</string>
		<string lang="uk">Остання Глава:</string>
</set>
<set id="epilogue-1">
		<string lang="de">Oh nein ...</string>
		<string lang="en">Oh no ...</string>
		<string lang="fr">Oh non ...</string>
		<string lang="zh">哦不……</string>
		<string lang="jp">なんてこと……</string>
		<string lang="ru">О нет ...</string>
		<string lang="es">Oh no ...</string>
		<string lang="kr">세상에...</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Ah não ...</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">哦不……
</string>
		<string lang="uk">О ні ...</string>
</set>
<set id="epilogue-2">
		<string lang="de">... wir waren es, die die Gravistrophe verursacht haben?</string>
		<string lang="en">... it was us who caused the gravistrophe?</string>
		<string lang="fr">... c'est nous qui avons causé la gravistrophe ?</string>
		<string lang="zh">……当初造成引力扭转的，是我们？</string>
		<string lang="jp">……重力大変動の原因は$br$自分たち？</string>
		<string lang="ru">... это мы вызвали гравистрофу?</string>
		<string lang="es">... ¿fuimos nosotros quienes causamos la gravistrofe?</string>
		<string lang="kr">...중력 재앙을 일으킨 건 우리였던 건가?</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">... fomos nós que causamos a gravistrofe?</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">……當初造成引力扭轉的，是我們？
</string>
		<string lang="uk">...це ми спричинили гравістрофу?</string>
</set>
<set id="epilogue-3">
		<string lang="de">Klicke auf das Discord-Symbol, um eine exklusive Rolle zu erhalten.$p$Vielen Dank, dass du Rogue Voltage spielst.</string>
		<string lang="en">Click on the Discord icon to receive an exclusive role.$p$Thank you for playing Rogue Voltage.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Cliquez sur l'icône Discord pour recevoir un rôle exclusif.$p$Merci d'avoir joué à Rogue Voltage.</string>
		<string lang="zh">点击Discord图标获得您的Discord频道专属角色。$p$再次感谢您对《末日电涌》的支持。</string>
		<string lang="jp">Discordアイコンクリックで、限定ロール入手。$p$Rogue Voltageのプレイありがとう。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Нажмите на значок Discord, чтобы получить эксклюзивную роль.$p$Спасибо, что играли в Rogue Voltage.</string>
		<string lang="kr">디스코드 아이콘을 클릭해 한정 역할을 수령하실 수 있습니다.$p$로그 볼티지를 플레이해주셔서 감사합니다.</string>
		<string lang="es">Haz clic en el icono de Discord para recibir un rol exclusivo.$p$Gracias por jugar a Rogue Voltage.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">點擊Discord圖示以獲得您的Discord頻道專屬角色。 $p$再次感謝您對《末日電湧》的支持。</string>
		<string lang="uk">Натискай на іконку Discord, щоб отримати ексклюзивну роль.$p$Дякую за гру в Rogue Voltage.</string>
</set>
<set id="name-act-1">
		<string lang="de">Quer durch die$br$sichere Zone</string>
		<string lang="en">Across the$br$Perimeter</string>
		<string lang="fr">En Traversant$br$le Perimètre</string>
		<string lang="zh">穿越边界</string>
		<string lang="jp">境界を超えて</string>
		<string lang="ru">Через Периметр</string>
		<string lang="es">Atravesando el$br$Perímetro</string>
		<string lang="kr">경계를 넘어</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Atravessando o$br$Perímetro</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">穿越$br$邊界
</string>
		<string lang="uk">За Периметр</string>
</set>
<set id="name-act-2">
		<string lang="de">Der Ummauerte Garten</string>
		<string lang="en">The Walled Garden</string>
		<string lang="fr">Le Jardin Enclos</string>
		<string lang="zh">围墙内的伊甸园</string>
		<string lang="jp">楽園は檻の中</string>
		<string lang="ru">Огороженный Сад</string>
		<string lang="es">El Jardín Amurallado</string>
		<string lang="kr">벽 안의 정원</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">O Jardim Murado</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">圍牆內的伊甸園
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Огороджений сад</string>
</set>
<set id="prologue-1">
		<string lang="de">Es ist das Jahr 3000 und nochwas.</string>
		<string lang="en">The year is 3000 and something.</string>
		<string lang="fr">L'année est 3000 et quelques.</string>
		<string lang="zh">公元3000左右。</string>
		<string lang="jp">西暦3000年ごろ</string>
		<string lang="ru">Год 3000 или что-то вроде того.</string>
		<string lang="es">Es el año 3000 y algo.</string>
		<string lang="kr">3000 몇 년 가량의 일입니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">O ano é 3000 e alguma coisa.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">西元3000左右。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Рік 3000 якийсь-там.</string>
</set>
<set id="prologue-2">
		<string lang="de">Die Welt ....</string>
		<string lang="en">The world ...</string>
		<string lang="fr">Le monde ...</string>
		<string lang="zh">整个世界……</string>
		<string lang="jp">世界は……</string>
		<string lang="ru">Мир ....</string>
		<string lang="es">El mundo ...</string>
		<string lang="kr">세계는...</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">O mundo ...</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">整個世界……
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Світ ...</string>
</set>
<set id="prologue-2b">
		<string lang="de">nunja ....</string>
		<string lang="en">well ...</string>
		<string lang="fr">bon ...</string>
		<string lang="zh">砰</string>
		<string lang="jp">まあ……</string>
		<string lang="ru">ну ...</string>
		<string lang="es">bueno ...</string>
		<string lang="kr">음...</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">bem ...</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">砰
</string>
		<string lang="uk">ну ...</string>
</set>
<set id="prologue-3">
		<string lang="de">sie wurde leider$br$ziemlich zerstört.</string>
		<string lang="en">let's say it's gotten$br$pretty much destroyed.</string>
		<string lang="fr">il malheureusement$br$a été détruit.</string>
		<string lang="zh">可以说是$br$几乎变成了一片废墟。</string>
		<string lang="jp">大崩壊した$br$そう言える</string>
		<string lang="ru">давайте скажем, что он был$br$типа разрушен.</string>
		<string lang="es">digamos que ha quedado$br$bastante destrozado.</string>
		<string lang="kr">세계가 꽤$br$파괴된 상태라고 가정해보죠.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">digamos que foi$br$bastante destruído.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">可以說是$br$幾乎變成了一片廢墟。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">скажімо так$br$ - фактично знищено.</string>
</set>
<set id="prologue-4">
		<string lang="de">Die wenigen Überlebenden der $b$Gravistrophe$/b$ leben in verstreuten Wohnlagern von gravitonischen Energiespitzen.</string>
		<string lang="en">The few survivors of the $b$Gravistrophe$/b$$br$live in scattered campsites$br$off gravitonic energy spikes.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Les quelques survivants de la $b$Gravistrophe$/b$$br$vivent dans des campements éparpillés$br$de crêtes d'énergie gravitonique.</string>
		<string lang="zh">$b$引力扭转$/b$后的少数幸存者$br$纷纷避开引力高峰区$br$四处安营扎寨。</string>
		<string lang="jp">$b$重力大変動$/b$$br$わずかな生存者は$br$散在して野営していた$br$重力スパイクを避けて</string>
		<string lang="ru">Несколько выживших из $b$Гравистрофы$/b$$br$живут в разбросанных лагерях, укрываясь от гравитонных энергетических шипов.</string>
		<string lang="es">Los pocos supervivientes de la $b$gravístrofe$/b$$br$viven en campamentos dispersados$br$sobre picos de energía gravitónica.</string>
		<string lang="kr">$b$중력 재앙$/b$에서 살아남은 소수의 생존자들은$br$중력 에너지 폭주와 멀찍이 떨어진 야영지에$br$뿔뿔이 흩어져 살고 있습니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Os poucos sobreviventes da $b$gravístrofe$/b$$br$vivem em acampamentos dispersos$br$de picos de energia gravitônica.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">$b$引力扭轉$/b$後的少數倖存者$br$紛紛避開引力高峰區$br$四處安營紮寨。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Купка тих, хто вижив після $b$Гравістрофи$/b$ $br$живе у поодиноких таборах,$br$ ховаючись від стрибків гравітонічної енергії.</string>
</set>
</localization>
