<localization>
<set id="name-chapter-bogmarshes">
		<string lang="de">Moorsümpfe</string>
		<string lang="en">Bogmarshes</string>
		<string lang="fr">Marais palustre</string>
		<string lang="zh">沼泽</string>
		<string lang="jp">沼地</string>
		<string lang="ru">Болотные топи</string>
		<string lang="es">Pantanos</string>
		<string lang="kr">습지</string>
</set>
<set id="name-chapter-dinosaurgraveyard">
		<string lang="de">Dynosaurier-Friedhof</string>
		<string lang="en">Dynosaur Graveyard</string>
		<string lang="fr">Cimetière de Dynosaures</string>
		<string lang="zh">Dynosaur Graveyard</string>
		<string lang="jp">Dynosaur Graveyard</string>
		<string lang="kr">Dynosaur Graveyard</string>
</set>
<set id="name-chapter-lavacaves">
		<string lang="de">Lava-Höhlen</string>
		<string lang="en">Lava Caves</string>
		<string lang="fr">Cavernes de lave</string>
		<string lang="zh">Lava Caves</string>
		<string lang="jp">Lava Caves</string>
		<string lang="kr">Lava Caves</string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-bogmarshes">
		<string lang="de">Normalerweise zersetzen sich Moore langsam, aber durch das instabile Grav.-Feld hier vergeht die Zeit stoßweise.$br$Torf wird an einem Nachmittag zu Kohle. Die Mangroven wachsen so schnell, dass man sie quietschen hört. Bleibt von den Pilzsporen fern, sonst verpasst ihr das Abendessen!$br$Außerdem – holt euch keine nassen Socken.</string>
		<string lang="en">Bogs are supposed to decompose slowly, but with the unstable grav. field here, time moves in fits and starts.$br$Peat turns into coal in an afternoon. The mangroves grow so quick you can hear ‘em squeak. Don’t get near the mushroom spores, or you’ll blink and miss dinner!$br$Also, try to keep your socks dry.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Les marais sont censés se décomposer lentement, mais avec le champ grav. instable ici, le temps passe en saccades.$br$L'après-midi, le tourbe se transforme en charbon. Les mangroves poussent si vite que vous pouvez les entendre gémir. Ne vous approchez pas des spores de champignons, sinon vous manquerez le dîner!$br$</string>
		<string lang="zh">沼泽通常是缓慢腐败的，但在不稳定的引力场中，时间可能会断断续续。$br$泥炭在一个下午内变成煤。红树林高速生长，吱吱作响。不要靠近蘑菇孢子，否则你可能会在一眨眼间错过下一顿晚餐$br$</string>
		<string lang="jp">沼地は通常はゆっくりと分解されるはずですが、ここに不安定な重力場があるため、時間は一瞬一瞬になります。$br$石炭は午後になると石炭になります。マングローブはとても速く育ち、ゴーグルをかけているときに聞こえる音がします。キノコの孢子に近づかないでください、そうしないと夕食を食べるのを見逃してしまいます$br$</string>
		<string lang="ru">Болота должны разлагаться медленно, но с нестабильным грав. полем здесь, время движется рывками.$br$Торф превращается в уголь за одно послеполуденное время. Мангровые деревья растут так быстро, что вы можете услышать их писк. Не подходите к спорам грибов, иначе вы моргнете и пропустите обед!$br$</string>
		<string lang="es">Los pantanos se supone que se descomponen lentamente, pero con el campo grav. inestable aquí, el tiempo se mueve a tirones.$br$La turba se convierte en carbón en una tarde. Los manglares crecen tan rápido que puedes oírlos chirriar. ¡No te acerques a las esporas de los hongos, o parpadearás y te perderás la cena!$br$</string>
		<string lang="kr">습지는 습기가 많습니다. 습지는 습기가 많습니다. 습지는 습기가 가장 많습니다.$br$우리는 거대한 두꺼비와 지성을 가진 버섯을 볼 수 있습니다. 누군가가 뒤에 모듈을 놓아 두었는지 눈을 뜨고 있으십시오. $br$</string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-bogmarshes-cycle5">
		<string lang="de">Moore sind feucht. Sümpfe sind feucht. Die Moorsümpfe sind die Feuchtigkeit schlechthin.$br$Wir werden auf Riesenkröten und intelligente Pilze treffen. Haltet die Augen nach Modulen offen, die von Menschen zurückgelassen wurden.</string>
		<string lang="en">Bogs are wet. Marshes are wet. The Bogmarshes are the wettest of the wet.$br$We’re liable to see giant toads and sentient mushrooms. Keep your eyes peeled for any modules people have left behind. </string>
		<string lang="fr">Les marais sont humides. Les palustres sont humides. Les marais palustres sont les plus humides de tous.$br$Nous allons rencontrer des crapauds géants et des champignons intelligents. Gardez les yeux ouverts pour récupérer des modules que des gens ont pu laisser derrière eux. </string>
		<string lang="zh">沼泽是潮湿的，湿地是潮湿的。湿沼地是个极度潮湿的地方。$br$我们可能会看到巨大的蟾蜍和有意识的蘑菇。请留意关注前人留在这里的模块。</string>
		<string lang="jp">沼地は濡れている。$br$巨大なカエルと知能を持ったキノコに出会うかもしれない。人々が残したモジュールを見つけるために目を凝らしてください。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Болота влажные. Топи влажные. Болотные топи – самые влажные из всех.$br$Мы можем увидеть гигантских жаб и разумных грибов. Держите глаза открытыми на случай, если кто-то оставил за собой модули. </string>
		<string lang="es">Las Ciénagas son húmedas. Las Marismas son húmedas. Las Cienarismas son las humedérrimas de todas. Es probable que veamos sapos gigantes y hongos inteligentes. Mantén los ojos abiertos por si alguien ha dejado módulos atrás. </string>
		<string lang="kr">습지는 습기가 많습니다. 습지는 습기가 많습니다. 습지는 습기가 가장 많습니다.$br$우리는 거대한 두꺼비와 지성을 가진 버섯을 볼 수 있습니다. 누군가가 뒤에 모듈을 놓아 두었는지 눈을 뜨고 있으십시오. </string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-dinosaurgraveyard">
		<string lang="de">Story N/A</string>
		<string lang="en">Story N/A</string>
		<string lang="fr">Story N/A</string>
		<string lang="zh">Story N/A</string>
		<string lang="jp">Story N/A</string>
		<string lang="kr">Story N/A</string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-lavacaves">
		<string lang="de">Sei vorsichtig, die Felsen sind hier rasiermesserscharf.$br$Das Krabbeln in der Dunkelheit ist eine weitere seltsame Sammlung von Kreaturen. Sie haben hier unten für komprimierte Eonen gelebt und können den Eruptionen leicht ausweichen.$br$Wir müssen aufpassen wohin und vor allem wann wir treten, um die Lavastöße zu vermeiden.$br$Wir sollten wahrscheinlich unsere Mäntel ausziehen.</string>
		<string lang="en">Be careful, the rocks are razor-sharp here.$br$That skittering in the dark is another strange collection of creatures. They have lived down here for compressed eons and can easily avoid the eruptions.$br$We will have to watch when and where we step in order to avoid the emissions of lava.$br$We should probably take off our coats.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Ces ondulations dans la pénombre sont la manifestation d'étranges créatures. Elles vivent ici bas pour des eons compressés et peuvent aisément éviter les éruptions.$br$Nous devrons être vigilant à quand et où nous devrons poser nos pieds, afin d'éviter les éruptions volcaniques.$br$Nous devrions enelever nos vestes.</string>
		<string lang="zh">Be careful, the rocks are razor-sharp here.$br$That skittering in the dark is another strange collection of creatures. They have lived down here for compressed eons and can easily avoid the eruptions.$br$We will have to watch when and where we step in order to avoid the emissions of lava.$br$We should probably take off our coats.</string>
		<string lang="jp">Be careful, the rocks are razor-sharp here.$br$That skittering in the dark is another strange collection of creatures. They have lived down here for compressed eons and can easily avoid the eruptions.$br$We will have to watch when and where we step in order to avoid the emissions of lava.$br$We should probably take off our coats.</string>
		<string lang="kr">Be careful, the rocks are razor-sharp here.$br$That skittering in the dark is another strange collection of creatures. They have lived down here for compressed eons and can easily avoid the eruptions.$br$We will have to watch when and where we step in order to avoid the emissions of lava.$br$We should probably take off our coats.</string>
</set>
</localization>
