<localization>
    <set id="name-chapter-gravitonicrift">
        <string lang="de">Gravitonischer Spalt</string>
        <string lang="en">Gravitonic Rift</string>
        <string lang="fr">Fissure gravitonique</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Гравітонічний Розлом</string>
</set>
    <set id="name-chapter-heartofthestorm">
        <string lang="de">Auge des Sturms</string>
        <string lang="en">Heart of the Storm</string>
        <string lang="fr">Cœur de la tempête</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Серце Шторму</string>
</set>
    <set id="name-chapter-thunderplains">
        <string lang="de">Donnersteppe</string>
        <string lang="en">Thunder Plains</string>
        <string lang="fr">Plaines de Tonnerre</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Громові Рівнини</string>
</set>
    <set id="name-chapter-silocity">
        <string lang="de">Silostadt</string>
        <string lang="en">Silo City</string>
        <string lang="fr">Cité Silo</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Силос Сіті</string>
</set>
    <set id="story-chapter-silocity">
        <string lang="de">Die Ruinen von was einmal eine Stadt gewesen sein muss. Hier gibt es sicherlich tolle Module.$br$Allerdings ist der Grund, warum hier überhaupt noch wertvolles Zeug rumliegt, dass alles voller Fallen und gefährlicher Apparate ist.</string>
        <string lang="en">The ruins of what appears to have been a city. Great gear should be around here. $br$That said, the only reason valuable stuff is still lying around out in the open is that there are traps and contraptions everywhere.</string>
        <string lang="fr">Les restes de la Cité Silo. De l'équipement de grande qualité doit se trouver ici.$br$Cependant, la seule raison que des choses de valeurs soient trouvables à ciel ouvert, est qu'il y a des gangs de renards voraces au pouvoir.</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Руїни того, що, здається, колись було містом. Тут має бути чудове спорядження. $br$Проте єдина причина, чому цінні речі все ще валяються просто неба, полягає в тому, що тут скрізь підступні пастки.</string>
</set>
    <set id="name-chapter-silvestria">
        <string lang="de">Silvestria</string>
        <string lang="en">Silvestria</string>
        <string lang="fr">Silvestria</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Сільвестрія</string>
</set>
    <set id="story-chapter-thunderplains">
        <string lang="de">Story n/a</string>
        <string lang="en">Story n/a</string>
        <string lang="fr">Story n/a</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Історія н/д</string>
</set>
    <set id="story-chapter-silvestria">
        <string lang="de">Die feuchte Luft hier ist gut für die Pflanzen. Oder die Pflanzen machen es hier feucht. Ursprung ungeklärt.$br$Ich bin hier schon lange nicht mehr gewesen. Ich weiß gar nicht, was ich erwarten soll.$br$Ups. Diese Fußabdrücke sehen groß aus.</string>
        <string lang="en">The damp here is good for the plants. Or the plants are making it damp here. Source’s not totally clear.$br$I haven’t been out here in a long time. I don’t even know what to expect.$br$Yikes. Those footprints look big.</string>
        <string lang="fr">Le marais est bon pour les plantes. Ou les plantes créées leur propre marais. Leur source n'est pas très clair. Je n’ai pas été loin longtemps. Je ne sais pas à quoi m'attendre.$br$Oh là là, ces traces de pieds semblent grandes...</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Вогкість тут корисна для рослин. Або рослини створюють тут вогкість. Джерело не зовсім зрозуміле.$br$Я давно тут не був. Я навіть не знаю, чого чекати.$br$Ой. Ці сліди такі великі.</string>
</set>
    <set id="story-chapter-silvestria-cycle3">
        <string lang="de">Üppiger gravioaktiver Wald, so weit das Auge reicht (was nicht allzu weit ist, denn der Wuchs ist überaus dicht).$br$Farn, Sumpfgräser und Kakteen wachsen in kleinen Lichtungen. Der exotischste Dschungel, den ich je gesehen habe. Auch der mit der größten Bienenvolk.$br$Die Bienen scheinen heute besonders wütend.</string>
        <string lang="en">Lush gravioactive forest as far as you can see, which ain’t too far, because it is thick. Ferns, marsh grasses, and cactuses grow in little pockets of sunlight.$br$Most eclectic jungle I’ve ever seen. Also the one with the largest bee population.$br$The bees seem especially angry today.</string>
        <string lang="fr">Les forêts gravioactiveux de Silvestria aussi loin que vous pouvez voir, ce qui n'est pas très loin, car c'est opaque. Fougères, graminées, et cactus grandissent tel des rayons de lumières.$br$La forêt la plus électrique que j'ai jamais vu. Aussi celle avec le plus d'abeilles.$br$Aujourd'hui, elles semblent particulièrement énervées.</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Пишний гравіоактивний ліс куди сягає око (а сягає недалеко, бо ліс густий).$br$Папороті, болотні трави та кактуси ростуть у маленьких кишеньках сонячного світла. Найекзотичніші джунглі, які я коли-небудь бачив. Ще й з найбільшою популяцією бджіл.$br$Сьогодні бджоли здаються особливо злими.</string>
</set>
    <set id="story-chapter-gravitonicrift">
        <string lang="de">Story n/a</string>
        <string lang="en">Story n/a</string>
        <string lang="fr">Story n/a</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Історія н/д</string>
</set>
    <set id="story-chapter-heartofthestorm">
        <string lang="de">Story n/a</string>
        <string lang="en">Story n/a</string>
        <string lang="fr">Story n/a</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Історія н/д</string>
</set>
    <set id="story-chapter-walledgarden">
        <string lang="de">Story N/A</string>
        <string lang="en">Story N/A</string>
        <string lang="fr">Story N/A</string>
    		<string lang="uk">Історія Н/Д</string>
</set>
</localization>
