<localization>
<set id="name-chapter-caves">
		<string lang="de">Kristallhöhlen</string>
		<string lang="en">Crystal Caverns</string>
		<string lang="fr">Cavernes Cristallines</string>
		<string lang="zh">水晶洞穴</string>
		<string lang="jp">水晶洞窟</string>
		<string lang="ru">Кристальные Пещеры</string>
		<string lang="es">Cavernas de Cristal</string>
		<string lang="kr">크리스탈 동굴</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Cavernas de Cristal</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">水晶洞穴
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Кришталеві Печери</string>
</set>
<set id="name-chapter-sewers">
		<string lang="de">Die Kanalisation</string>
		<string lang="en">The Sewers</string>
		<string lang="fr">Les Égouts</string>
		<string lang="zh">下水道</string>
		<string lang="jp">下水道</string>
		<string lang="ru">Канализация</string>
		<string lang="es">Las Alcantarillas</string>
		<string lang="kr">하수구</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Esgotos</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">下水道
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Каналізація</string>
</set>
<set id="name-chapter-tutorial">
		<string lang="de">Tutorial</string>
		<string lang="en">Tutorial</string>
		<string lang="fr">Tutoriel</string>
		<string lang="zh">教程</string>
		<string lang="jp">チュートリアル</string>
		<string lang="ru">Обучение</string>
		<string lang="es">Tutorial</string>
		<string lang="kr">튜토리얼</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Tutorial</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">教程
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Навчання</string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-caves">
		<string lang="de">“Hast du deine Stiefel? Es geht abwärts.$p$Es sind Impulse aus Grav.-Ladung, die von den Felswänden hier zurückgeworfen werden.$p$Dadurch produziert die Umgebung eine zuverlässige Energiequelle für all die merkwürdigen Kreaturen, die sich daran angepasst haben.”</string>
		<string lang="en">“You got your boots? We’re heading down.$p$It's impulses of grav. charge, that are reflecting off the cave walls in here.$p$Unfortunately, and thanks to that, this environment provides a constant supply of sustenance for any strange creature that has adapted to living off of it.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">“Tu as tes bottes? On descend.$p$C'est des impulsions de charge grav. qui sont réfléchies par les parois de la grotte ici.$p$Malheureusement, et grâce à cela, cet environnement fournit une source constante de nourriture pour toute créature étrange qui s'est adaptée à vivre de cela.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">穿靴子了没？我们要下去了。$p$洞穴墙壁上来回反射的，就是引力脉冲。$p$很不幸，正是这些引力荷为里面的生物提供了源源不断的养料，使它们变成了适应环境的怪物。</string>
		<string lang="jp">ブーツ履いた？下へ降りるよ。$p$ここじゃ、重力インパルスに襲われるからね。洞窟の壁面に反射するんだ。$p$残念だけど、ここに適応した奇妙な生物たちは、恒常的に環境から恩恵を受けてるってわけ。</string>
		<string lang="ru">“Ты взял свои сапоги? Мы спускаемся.$p$Это импульсы грав. заряда, которые отражаются от стен пещеры.$p$К сожалению, а так же к счастью, это окружение обеспечивает постоянное снабжение пищей любого странного существа, которое приспособилось к жизни за счёт этого.”</string>
		<string lang="es">“¿Tienes tus botas? Nos dirigimos hacia abajo.$p$Son los impulsos de carga grav., que se reflejan en las paredes de la cueva.$p$Desafortunadamente, y gracias a eso, este entorno proporciona un suministro constante de sustento para cualquier extraña criatura que se haya adaptado a vivir de él.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">장화는 준비했나요? 이제 내려갈 겁니다.$p$여기에서는 중력 전하의 충격이 동굴 벽에 반사되고 있습니다.$p$유감스럽게도, 여기에도 운 좋게 주변 환경에 적응한 채 안정적으로 영양분을 공급받으며 살아가는 생명체들이 존재합니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">“Você tem suas botas? Estamos indo para baixo.$p$São impulsos de carga grav., que estão refletindo nas paredes da caverna.$p$Infelizmente, e graças a isso, este ambiente fornece um suprimento constante de sustento para qualquer criatura estranha que tenha se adaptado a viver dele.”</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">穿靴子了沒？我們要下去了。$br$洞穴牆壁上來回反射的，就是引力脈衝。$br$很不幸，正是這些引力荷為裏面的生物提供了源源不斷的養料，使它們變成了適應環境的怪物。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">«Чоботи взяв? Ми спускаємось.$p$Тут імпульси гравізаряду відбиваються від стінок печери.$p$Таким чином це середовище надійно забезпечує енергією будь-яких дивних істот, що пристосувалися до її споживання.»</string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-sewers">
		<string lang="de">“Nach der ersten Grav.-Welle suchten viele Überlebende in der Kanalisation Zuflucht, nur um festzustellen, dass auch hier die Zeitverzerrungen wirksam waren.$p$Einige Abschnitte aus Beton waren in einem Sekundenbruchteil um tausend Jahre gealtert, wurden brüchig und brachen zusammen.$p$Andere wurden cremig wie am Tag, an dem sie gegossen wurden.”</string>
		<string lang="en">“After the initial grav. wave, many survivors sought refuge in the sewers, only to discover that also here the time distortions had taken effect.$p$Some sections of concrete had aged a thousand years in a second, becoming brittle and crumbled.$p$Others became creamy like on the day they were poured.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">“Après la première vague grav., nombreux survivants ont établi leur camp dans les égouts, seulement pour découvrir que les distorsions temporelles avaient également eu effet ici.$p$Certaines sections de béton avaient vieilli de mille ans en une seconde, devenant fragiles et s'effondrant.$p$D'autres sont devenues crémeuses comme le jour où elles ont été coulées.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">最初的引力波平息之后，许多幸存者来到下水道安营扎寨，却发现这里也受到了时间扭曲的影响。$p$有一些混凝土瞬间经历了千年的风霜，变得脆弱不堪。$p$还有一些则回到最初还未凝固时的样子。</string>
		<string lang="jp">初期の重力波動の後、多くの生存者が下水道を野営地とした。しかし、そこにも時間の歪みが発生していた。$p$ある場所では、コンクリートが一瞬で千年経つほど風化し、脆くも崩れ落ちた。$p$別の場所では、その日に流し込まれたばかりのようにクリーミーになった。</string>
		<string lang="ru">“После первой грав. волны, многие выжившие разбили лагерь в канализации, но обнаружили, что временные искажения вступили в силу и здесь.$p$Некоторые участки бетона состарились на тысячу лет за секунду и превратились в пыль. $p$Другие размякли, как в день заливки.”</string>
		<string lang="es">“Después de la primera onda grav., muchos supervivientes establecieron un campamento en las alcantarillas, solo para descubrir que también aquí las distorsiones temporales habían tenido efecto.$p$Algunas secciones de hormigón habían envejecido mil años en un segundo, volviéndose quebradizas y desmoronándose.$p$Otras se volvieron cremosas como el día en que fueron vertidas.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">최초의 중력파 이후 많은 생존자들이 하수구에 야영지를 세웠지만, 결국 시간 왜곡이 하수구에도 영향을 줬다는 사실을 깨닫게 될 뿐이었습니다.$p$콘크리트 중 일부분은 순식간에 천 년의 세월이 지나 깨지고 바스라졌습니다.$p$다른 부분은 콘크리트가 처음 부어졌던 날처럼 걸쭉해졌습니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">“Depois da onda grav., muitos sobreviventes montaram acampamento nos esgotos, apenas para descobrir que também aqui as distorções temporais haviam surtido efeito.$p$Algumas seções de concreto envelheceram mil anos em um segundo, tornaram-se quebradiças e desmoronaram.$p$Outras ficaram cremosas como no dia em que foram despejadas.”</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">最初的引力波平息之後，許多倖存者來到下水道安營紮寨，卻發現這裏也受到了時間扭曲的影響。$br$有一些混凝土瞬間經歷了千年的風霜，變得脆弱不堪。$br$還有一些則回到最初還未凝固時的樣子。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">«Після початкової гравіхвилі, багато тих, хто вижив, шукали притулку в каналізації, але виявилося, що і тут спотворення часу далося взнаки.$p$Деякі ділянки бетону постаріли на тисячу років за секунду та розсипалися на пил.$p$Інші перетворилися на крем, наче їх тільки-но залили.»</string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-tutorial">
		<string lang="de">Unsere Geschichte beginnt an einem Tag wie jeder andere.$p$$slopperjohnson$, unser postapokalyptischer Paketbote, ist auf der Suche nach Modulen, die er zurück in sein Camp bringen kann.</string>
		<string lang="en">Our story begins on a day like any other.$p$$slopperjohnson$, our post-apocalyptic parcel carrier, is looking for modules to bring back to his camp.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Notre histoire commence un jour comme les autres.$p$$slopperjohnson$, notre livreur post-apocalyptique, est à la recherche de modules pour les ramener à son camp.</string>
		<string lang="zh">我们的故事从普通的一天开始。$p$$slopperjohnson$，我们的末世送货员，正在寻找能够带回营地的$b$模块$/b$。</string>
		<string lang="jp">我らが物語は、なんてことない一日から始まる。$p$$slopperjohnson$、我らがポストアポカリプス宅配人は、キャンプに持ち帰る$b$モジュール$/b$を探していた。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Наша история начинается в день, похожий на любой другой.$p$$slopperjohnson$, наш постапокалиптический курьер, ищет модули, которые можно принести в лагерь.</string>
		<string lang="es">Nuestra historia comienza en un día como cualquier otro.$p$$slopperjohnson$, nuestro transportista de paquetes post-apocalíptico, está buscando $b$módulos$/b$ para llevar de vuelta a su campamento.</string>
		<string lang="kr">이야기의 시작은 여느 날과 크게 다르지 않았습니다.$p$포스트 아포칼립스 소포 배달부인 우리의 $slopperjohnson$은, 야영지로 가지고 돌아갈 모듈을 찾고 있었습니다.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Nossa história começa em um dia como qualquer outro.$p$$slopperjohnson$, nosso transportador de encomendas pós-apocalíptico, está procurando módulos para levar de volta ao seu acampamento.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">我們的故事從普通的一天開始。$br$$slopperjohnson$，我們的末世送貨員，正在尋找能夠帶回營地的$b$模組$/b$。
</string>
		<string lang="uk">Наша історія починається одного нічим не примітного дня.$p$ $slopperjohnson$, наш пост-апокаліптичний кур'єр, шукав модулі, які б він міг принести до свого табору.</string>
</set>
</localization>
