<localization>
<set id="name-chapter-bogmarshes">
		<string lang="de">Moorsümpfe</string>
		<string lang="en">Bogmarshes</string>
		<string lang="fr">Marais palustre</string>
		<string lang="zh">泥沼</string>
		<string lang="jp">湿原</string>
		<string lang="ru">Болотные топи</string>
		<string lang="es">Pantanos</string>
		<string lang="kr">수렁늪</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Pântanos</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">泥沼
</string>
</set>
<set id="name-chapter-dinosaurgraveyard">
		<string lang="de">Dynosaurier-Friedhof</string>
		<string lang="en">Dynosaur Graveyard</string>
		<string lang="fr">Cimetière de Dynosaures</string>
		<string lang="zh">恐龙坟场</string>
		<string lang="jp">恐竜墓</string>
		<string lang="ru">Кладбище динозавров</string>
		<string lang="es">Cementerio de Dinosaurios</string>
		<string lang="kr">공룡의 무덤</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Cemitério de Dinossauros</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">恐龍墳場
</string>
</set>
<set id="name-chapter-eden">
		<string lang="de">Eden</string>
		<string lang="en">Eden</string>
		<string lang="fr">Eden</string>
		<string lang="zh">伊甸园</string>
		<string lang="jp">エデン</string>
		<string lang="ru">Эдем</string>
		<string lang="es">Edén</string>
		<string lang="kr">에덴</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Éden</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">伊甸園
</string>
</set>
<set id="name-chapter-lavacaves">
		<string lang="de">Vulkan</string>
		<string lang="en">Volcano</string>
		<string lang="fr">Volcan</string>
		<string lang="zh">火山</string>
		<string lang="jp">火山</string>
		<string lang="ru">Вулкан</string>
		<string lang="es">Volcán</string>
		<string lang="kr">화산</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Vulcão</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">火山
</string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-bogmarshes">
		<string lang="de">“Normalerweise zersetzen sich Moore langsam, aber durch das instabile Grav.-Feld hier vergeht die Zeit stoßweise.$p$Torf wird an einem Nachmittag zu Kohle. Die Mangroven wachsen so schnell, dass man sie quietschen hört.$p$Bleibt von den Pilzsporen fern, sonst verpasst ihr das Abendessen!”</string>
		<string lang="en">“Bogs are supposed to decompose slowly, but with the unstable grav. field here, time moves in fits and starts.$p$Peat turns into coal in an afternoon. The mangroves grow so quick you can hear ‘em squeak.$p$Don’t get near the mushroom spores, or you’ll blink and miss dinner!”</string>
		<string lang="fr">“Les marais sont censés se décomposer lentement, mais avec le champ grav. instable ici, le temps passe en saccades.$p$L'après-midi, le tourbe se transforme en charbon. Les mangroves poussent si vite que vous pouvez les entendre gémir.$p$Ne vous approchez pas des spores de champignons, sinon vous manquerez le dîner!”</string>
		<string lang="zh">沼泽通常是缓慢腐败的，但在不稳定的引力场中，时间可能会断断续续。$p$泥炭在一个下午内变成煤。红树林高速生长，吱吱作响。不要靠近蘑菇孢子，否则你可能会在一眨眼间错过下一顿晚餐$p$</string>
		<string lang="jp">沼地の腐敗はゆっくりと進むはずだけどねえ、ここいらは重力場が不安定だ。時間が断続的に飛んどるよ。$p$泥炭だって午後には石炭だ。マングローブなんて伸びる音が聞こえるよ。$p$キノコの胞子には近づくんじゃないよ。瞬き一つで夕食抜きだからね！</string>
		<string lang="ru">Болота должны разлагаться медленно, но с нестабильным грав. полем здесь, время движется рывками.$p$Торф превращается в уголь за один вечер. Мангровые деревья растут так быстро, что вы можете услышать их писк.$p$Не подходите к спорам грибов, иначе вы моргнете и пропустите ужин!</string>
		<string lang="es">“Los pantanos se supone que se descomponen lentamente, pero con el campo grav. inestable aquí, el tiempo se mueve a tirones.$p$La turba se convierte en carbón en una tarde. Los manglares crecen tan rápido que puedes oírlos chirriar.$p$No te acerques a las esporas de los hongos !O parpadearás y te perderás la cena!</string>
		<string lang="kr">늪지대는 서서히 부패해가고 있었지만, 불안정한 중력장으로 인해 시간이 제멋대로 변화하기 시작했습니다.$br$토탄은 오후가 될 무렵엔 석탄으로 변합니다. 맹그로브 나무는 너무 빨리 자라서 삐걱대는 소리가 들릴 정도입니다. 버섯 포자 근처에 가면 눈 깜짝할 사이 저녁 식사를 잃어버릴 수도 있습니다!$br$양말을 뽀송하게 유지하는 것도 잊지 마세요.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">“Pântanos são supostos se decompor lentamente, mas com o campo grav. instável aqui, o tempo se move em solavancos.$p$Turfa se transforma em carvão em uma tarde. Os manguezais crescem tão rápido que você pode ouvi-los chiar.$p$Não se aproxime das esporas dos cogumelos, ou você piscará e perderá o jantar!</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">沼澤內生物質的分解本應是個緩慢的過程，但此處不穩定的引力場使得時間的流動突兀而斷斷續續。$br$只消一個下午，泥炭就會結成煤層。紅樹林飛速生長，甚至聽得到木頭的吱呀聲。若是不小心吸入這裏蘑菇的孢子，有可能一眨眼就錯過了晚餐時間。$br$另外，小心別把襪子給弄濕了。
</string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-dinosaurgraveyard">
		<string lang="de">“In dieser Einöde muss ein mächtiger Grav.-Blast die Dinosaurier un-ausgestorben haben. Und sie dann wieder ausgelöscht haben. Und sie dann wieder-unausgestorben haben.$p$Nur so kann ich mir erklären, dass sie hier gleichzeitig versteinert sind und frei herumwandern.$p$Uff, diese Fußabdrücke sehen groß aus!”</string>
		<string lang="en">“In these wastelands, a powerful Grav. Blast must have unextincted the dinosaurs. And then re-extincted them. And then re-unextincted them.$p$This is the only explanation I can come up with for why they are at the same time fossilized and roaming the earth.$p$Yikes. Those footprints look big!</string>
		<string lang="fr"></string>
		<string lang="zh">这片荒野似乎发生过高烈度的引力震爆，导致恐龙重现世间——然后再度灭绝。然后又复活了。$p$不这么想，没法解释它们化石丧尸一样的状态。$p$哎呦喂。不管咋样，这些家伙留下的脚印可真是够大的啊！</string>
		<string lang="jp">この荒野じゃ、強力な重力爆発で恐竜が復活したに違いない。それから、また絶滅したんだ。$p$他に説明しようがないよ。だって地上で恐竜の化石化と繁栄が同時に進んでるんだよ。$p$わっ！この足跡の化石でっかっ！</string>
		<string lang="ru"></string>
		<string lang="es">"En éstos páramos, una poderosa Grav. Explosión ha debido desextinguir a los dinosaurios. Y entonces extinguirlos de nuevo. Y volverlos a desextinguir.$p$Es la única explicación que se me ocurre por la que estén fosilizados y deambulando la tierra al mismo tiempo.$p$Uf, ¡Éstas huellas parecen gigantes!"</string>
		<string lang="kr">이 황무지에 발생한 강력한 중력 돌풍이 공룡을 되살린 것으로 보입니다. 그리고 다시 멸종시켰고. 그리고 다시 되살린 거죠.$p$적어도 제가 아는한, 왜 화석이 된 공룡과 땅 위를 돌아다니는 공룡이 동시에 보이는 지를 설명할 수 있는 유일한 방법 같네요.$p$이런. 이 발자국은 꽤 커보이는데요!</string>
		<string lang="pt-br"></string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">這片荒野似乎發生過高烈度的引力震爆，導致恐龍重現世間——然後再度滅絕。然後又復活了。$p$不這麼想，沒法解釋它們化石喪屍一樣的狀態。$p$哎呦喂。不管咋樣，這些傢伙留下的腳印可真是夠大的啊！
</string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-eden">
		<string lang="de">Als der Verschlossene Garten angekündigt wurde, brach unter den Mächtigen ein heftiger Kampf aus. Niemand ergatterte einen Platz, ohne Blut an den Händen zu haben.$p$Jede Minute hinter dem Zeitdamm trocknet Jahrzehnte aus dem Leben unterhalb. Eine unheimliche Stille liegt über die Stadt – als wäre alles eingefroren.$p$Nach Tausenden von Jahren gibt es nichts mehr zu sagen.</string>
		<string lang="en">When the Walled Garden was announced, a most violent struggle erupted among the powerful. No one got to live here without blood on their hands.$p$Every minute behind the time dam dries up decades from all life below. An eerie silence blankets the city – as though everything is frozen.$p$After thousands of years, there’s nothing left to say.</string>
		<string lang="fr">Lorsque le Jardin Clos fut annoncé, une lutte violente éclata parmi les puissants. Personne ne put y vivre sans avoir du sang sur les mains.$p$Chaque minute derrière le barrage temporel assèche des décennies de vie en dessous. Un silence étrange recouvre la ville – comme si tout était gelé.$p$Après des milliers d'années, il n'y a plus rien à dire.</string>
		<string lang="zh">随着开辟伊甸园的计划公布，各大势力间爆发了残酷的斗争。如今居住其内的人们，没有一人手上未曾沾过同胞的鲜血。$br$时间坝后平缓流逝的每一分钟，代价都是其下诸多生命的数十年。城中笼罩着诡异的寂静——如同整座城都被冰封。$br$数千年的时光过去，这里的人再没有什么可说。</string>
		<string lang="jp">壁内庭園が公知された際、権力者の間で激しい争いが勃発しました。ここでは誰一人、その手を血に濡らしたことのない者はいません。$p$時間ダムの彼方では、1分で数十年分の生命が朽ち果てていきます。街は不気味な静寂に覆われていて、まるで、何もかもが凍てついているかのよう。$p$数千年後には、語る者もいません。</string>
		<string lang="ru">Когда был объявлен Запертый Сад, между могущественными разразилась жестокая борьба. Никто не мог здесь жить, не имея крови на руках.$p$Каждая минута за временной плотиной высушивает десятилетия жизни внизу. Жуткое молчание покрывает город – как будто всё замерло.$p$После тысячелетий, больше нечего сказать.</string>
		<string lang="es">Cuando se anunció el Jardín Hermético, estalló una lucha violenta entre los poderosos. Nadie consiguió vivir aquí sin sangre en sus manos.$p$Cada minuto detrás de la presa del tiempo seca décadas de vida de abajo. Un silencio inquietante cubre la ciudad, como si todo estuviera congelado.$p$Después de miles de años, no queda nada que decir.</string>
		<string lang="kr">벽 안의 정원이 사람들에게 공개되었을 때, 권력자들 사이에서는 격렬한 쟁탈전이 벌어졌습니다. 손에 피 한 방울 묻히지 않고 그곳에서 살게 된 사람은 아무도 없었죠.$br$시간 댐은 쉴 새 없이 아래에 있는 모든 생명체의 수십 년을 말라붙게 했습니다. 마치 모든 것이 얼어붙은 것처럼 - 기분 나쁜 고요함이 도시를 뒤덮고 있습니다.$br$수천 년이 지난 지금은 말할 것도 없겠죠.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">Quando o Jardim Fechado foi anunciado, uma luta violenta irrompeu entre os poderosos. Ninguém conseguiu viver aqui sem sangue em suas mãos.$p$Cada minuto atrás da barragem do tempo seca décadas de vida de baixo. Um silêncio inquietante cobre a cidade, como se tudo estivesse congelado.$p$Depois de milhares de anos, não há mais nada a dizer.</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">隨著開闢伊甸園的計畫公佈，各大勢力間爆發了殘酷的鬥爭。如今居住其內的人們，沒有一人手上未曾沾過同胞的鮮血。$br$時間壩後平緩流逝的每一分鐘，代價都是其下諸多生命的數十年。城中籠罩著詭異的寂靜——如同整座城都被冰封。$br$數千年的時光過去，這裏的人再沒有什麼可說。
</string>
</set>
<set id="story-chapter-lavacaves">
		<string lang="de">“Das Krabbeln in der Dunkelheit ist eine weitere seltsame Sammlung von Kreaturen. Sie haben hier unten für komprimierte Eonen gelebt und können den Eruptionen leicht ausweichen.$p$Wir müssen aufpassen wohin und vor allem wann wir treten, um die Lavastöße zu vermeiden.$p$Wir sollten wahrscheinlich unsere Mäntel ausziehen.”</string>
		<string lang="en">“That skittering in the dark is another strange collection of creatures. They have lived down here for compressed eons and can easily avoid the eruptions.$p$We will have to watch where and when we step in order to avoid the emissions of lava.$p$We should probably take off our coats.”</string>
		<string lang="fr">“Ces ondulations dans la pénombre sont la manifestation d'étranges créatures. Elles vivent ici bas pour des eons compressés et peuvent aisément éviter les éruptions.$p$Nous devrons être vigilant à où et quand nous devrons poser nos pieds, afin d'éviter les éruptions volcaniques.$p$Nous devrions enelever nos vestes.”</string>
		<string lang="zh">在黑暗中悉簌的，是另一群怪异的生物。它们生息于此的时间换算过来长达亿万年，因此可以轻松地避开火山喷发。$br$而我们要避免葬身熔岩，就必须格外注意落脚的位置和时机。$br$另外，外套最好也脱掉。</string>
		<string lang="jp">暗闇でギョロついてんのは、また別の変な生物どもが群れてるみてえだ。連中、圧縮された時間の中で長年暮らしてやがるから、噴火避けんのがずいぶんうめえ。$p$足元に注意して、溶岩の噴出避けねえと。$p$上着も脱いどかなきゃな。</string>
		<string lang="ru">“Это ползание в темноте – ещё одна странная коллекция существ. Они живут здесь в течение сжатых эонов и могут легко избегать извержений.$p$Нам придётся следить за тем, куда и когда мы ступаем, чтобы избежать выбросов лавы.$p$Мы, вероятно, должны снять свои пальто.”</string>
		<string lang="es">“Ese corretear en la oscuridad es otra extraña colección de criaturas. Han vivido aquí abajo por eones comprimidos y pueden eludir fácilmente las erupciones.$p$Debemos vigilar dónde y cuándo pisamos para evitar las emisiones de lava.$p$Probablemente deberíamos quitarnos los abrigos.”</string>
		<string lang="kr">어둠 속에서 꿈틀거리는 그것들은 또 다른 기묘한 생명체들의 집합체입니다. 그들은 압축된 영겁의 시간 동안 이 아래에서 지내왔으며, 그 덕에 분출을 쉽게 피할 수 있었습니다.$br$분출되는 용암을 피하기 위해서는 언제 발을 딛어야 할지 유심히 지켜봐야 할 것입니다.$br$아마 외투는 벗어야 될 것 같네요.</string>
		<string lang="pt-br">“Aquele rastejar na escuridão é outra estranha coleção de criaturas. Elas viveram aqui por éons comprimidos e podem facilmente evitar as erupções.$p$Precisaremos observar onde e quando pisamos para evitar as emissões de lava.$p$Provavelmente deveríamos tirar nossos casacos.”</string>
		<string lang="zh-tw">在黑暗中悉簌的，是另一群怪異的生物。它們生息於此的時間換算過來長達億萬年，因此可以輕鬆地避開火山噴發。$br$而我們要避免葬身熔岩，就必須格外注意落腳的位置和時機。$br$另外，外套最好也脫掉。
</string>
</set>
</localization>
